導剪藍光修復版片源  時間軸：mills
字幕翻譯製作：goodliuwu
托尼·斯科特作品
克裏斯蒂安·斯萊特
帕特麗夏·阿奎特
在《牢房搖滾》中  他就是鄉村搖滾的全部
In Jailhouse Rock, he was everything rockabilly is about.
我是說  他就是搖滾
I mean he is rockabilly:
刻薄  粗暴  下流  無禮
Mean, surly, nasty, rude.
在那部電影裏 他可以什麼都他媽不管不顧
In that movie, he couldn't give a fuck about nothin'.
就是搖啊滾啊  活得快  死得早
Except rocking and rolling, living fast, dying young...
留下一具好看的皮囊
and leaving a good-looking corpse.
我看著那個鄉村搖滾  我太想跟他一樣了
I watch that hillbilly and I want to be him so bad.
埃爾維斯[貓王]長相不錯
Elvis looked good.
我不是同性戀  不過…
Hey, I'm no fag. But...
埃爾維斯比多數女人要漂亮
Elvis was prettier than most women.
知道吧？多數女人
You know? Most women.
你看
You know
我總是說  如果我不得不操男人  我是說不得不
I always said, if I had to fuck a guy. I mean had to...
我的小命就靠它了
and my life depended on it...
我會操埃爾維斯
I'd fuck Elvis.
真的？
Really?
哦  他活著的時候  不是現在
Well, when he was alive, not now.
我不怪你
I don't blame you.
那麼  咱倆都操埃爾維斯
So, we'd both fuck Elvis.
認識有共同興趣的人挺好  對吧？
It's nice to meet people with common interests, ain't it?
嗯  貓王說夠了  你…你怎麼樣？
Well, enough about the King. How about you?
我什麼怎麼樣？
How about me what?
你今晚跟我去看電影怎麼樣？
How about you go to the movies with me tonight?
我們看什麼呢？
What are we gonna see?
千葉真一三片連映
A Sonny Chiba triple feature.
《殺人拳》《殺人拳2》
The Streetfighter, Return of the Streetfighter...
還有《女殺人拳》
and Sister Streetfighter.
千葉真一是誰？
Who's Sonny Chiba?
"千葉真一是誰？"
"Who's Sonny Chiba?"
他是沒有之一的今天最棒的武術電影演員
Well, he is, bar none, the finest actor working in martial arts movies today.
你要帶我去看一部功夫電影？
You want to take me to a kung fu movie?
三部功夫電影
Three kung fu movies.
我覺得不好
I don't think so.
真不是我的菜
Not really my cup of tea.
好的
All right.
片名：真實羅曼史
丹尼斯·霍珀
方·基默
加裏·奧德曼
布拉德·皮特
克裏斯托弗·沃肯
布隆森·皮諾切特
塞繆爾·傑克遜
邁克爾·拉帕波特
紹爾·魯賓內克
音樂：漢斯·季默
我不得不大老遠走弗羅裏達的塔拉哈西
I had to come all the way from the highways and byways...
的高速公路和小路
of Tallahassee, Florida...
到汽車城底特律  去找我的真愛
to Motor City, Detroit to find my true love.
即便你給我一百萬年去沉思
If you gave me a million years to ponder...
我永遠也猜不到真實羅曼史會跟底特律走到一起
I would never have guessed that true romance and Detroit would go together.
到今天  緊接著的那些事件全都像是一個遙遠的夢
And to this day, the events that followed all seem like a distant dream.
但這夢是真的
But the dream was real...
而且永遠改變了我們的生活
and was to change our lives forever.
我不斷地問克拉倫斯 為何我們的夢似乎在崩塌
I kept asking Clarence why our world seemed to be collapsing...
編劇：昆汀·塔倫蒂諾
一切好像如此糟爛
and everything seems so shitty.
而他說
And he'd say:
"世道如此  但別忘了…
"That's the way it goes. But don't forget...
"世道也會走向別處"
"...it goes the other way too".
那就是羅曼史
That's the way romance is.
通常它就是這樣走
Usually that's the way it goes.
但時不時地  它也往另一方向走
But every once in a while, it goes the other way too.
導演：托尼·斯科特
我心跳加速  時辰已到
My heart beats and there is time.
不要動  東條
Don't move, Tojo.
你很快會失去意識  讓氧氣進入…
You'll be unconscious soon to let oxygen....
這是一種古老的技巧
It's an ancient technique.
現在…
And...
氧氣
Oxygen.
來吧
Come.
噢  怎麼這樣  哦  老天  真對不起
Oh, look what happened! Oh, God, I am so sorry.
- 哦  沒關係  - 你沒事吧？
- Oh, it's okay.  - Are you okay?
對  我沒事
Yeah, I'm fine.
哦  老天  我真是笨透了
Oh, Jesus, I am the clumsiest person in the world.
沒事的  意外常有
That's all right. Accidents happen.
好棒的哲理  謝謝你這麼貼心
What a wonderful philosophy. Thanks for being a sweetheart.
因為你本可以發飆的
Because you could have been a real dick.
來吧  準備好了？
Come on! Ready?
是的
Yes.
拉裏  我們去哪兒？
Larry, where are we going?
瞧  我們不知道下一步會怎樣
Look, we don't know what will be coming next.
你是說你害怕了？
You mean you're scared?
嘿  洗衣店的衣服
Hey, laundromat clothes!
介意我抽煙嗎？
You mind if I smoke?
不
No.
聽著  你不介意跟講講我錯過了什麼嗎？
Listen, do you mind filling me in on what I missed?
不不
No, no.
看見了嗎？上面那個人  那是千葉真一
See this, that guy up there? It's Sonny Chiba.
那個東方人？
The Oriental?
對  那個穿黑衣的
Yeah, the one in black.
你要花生嗎？
You want a Goober?
不…好
No...Yeah.
看  電影開頭時他受雇來幹掉這個人
See, in the beginning of the movie he was hired to get this guy.
爆米花弄了你一身
You have got popcorn all over you.
謝謝  多謝
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
他是不是好人呢？
Is he supposed to be a good guy?
他算不上是個好人  只是個他媽的壞人
He ain't so much a good guy as he's just a bad motherfucker.
我是說  他收人錢  去幹掉別人  你知道
I mean, he gets paid by people to fuck guys up. You know.
你來看三部功夫電影？
You came to see three kung fu movies?
對……當然了  幹嘛不？
Yeah...Sure, why not?
沒什麼  沒什麼  你這女孩正合我心  如此而已
Nothing, nothing. You're a girl after my own heart. That's all.
你知道現在幾點了嗎？
Do you know what time it is?
大概12點
It's about 12:00.
我估計你得早起吧？
I suppose you've got to get up early, huh?
不  不見得  怎麼？
No, not particularly, how come?
就是  看完電影我喜歡吃個派…
It's just, after a movie, I like to go get some pie...
然後談論一番
and talk about it.
像是我的一個小傳統
Sort of a little tradition I have.
你看過一場好電影以後願意吃個派嗎？
Do you like to get pie after you see a good movie?
對  我喜歡看完電影吃派
Yeah, I love to get pie after a movie.
你想跟我去吃個派嗎？
Would you like to go get some pie with me?
我喜歡來點派
I'd love some pie.
我是說  在那部電影裏 他可以什麼都他媽不管不顧
Well, I mean. In that movie, he couldn't give a fuck about nothing.
就是搖啊滾啊  活得快  死得早…
Except rock-and-roll, living fast, dying young...
留下一具好看的皮囊
and leaving a good-looking corpse.
現在…
And...
貓王說夠了  你怎麼樣？
Enough about the King. How about you?
我什麼怎麼樣？
How about me what?
跟我說說  說說你自己
Well, tell me, tell me about yourself.
你想知道什麼？
What do you want to know?
哦  開個頭  你做什麼的？你哪裏人？
Well, for starters, what do you do? Where are you from?
什麼是你最喜歡的顏色？誰是你最喜歡的電影明星？
What's your favorite color? Who's your favorite movie star?
你喜歡什麼樣的音樂？
What kind of music do you like?
什麼東西讓你興奮  令你避開？
What are your turn-ons, your turn offs?
我猜大問題是  你有沒有…有沒有男人？
I guess the big question is, do you have a...do you have a fella?
好  再問我  一個個問
Okay, ask me again, one by one.
你做什麼的？
What do you do?
我不記得了
I don't remember.
- 你是哪裏人？  - 我不知道
- Where are you from? - I don't know.
你最喜歡的顏色？
What's your favorite color?
我不知道  黑色？
I don't know. Black?
- 誰是你最喜歡的電影明星？  - 伯特·雷諾茲
- Well, who's your favorite movie star? - Burt Reynolds.
你想吃一口我的派嗎？
Do you want a bite of my pie?
好的  我吃  一小口
Yes, I would. A little one.
好的
All right.
你還好吧？
You all right?
挺好吃的
It's good.
你喜歡嗎？
You like it?
你喜歡什麼樣的音樂？
What kind of music do you like?
菲爾·斯派特  女子團體的東西  他是個反叛者
Phil Spector. Girl-group stuff like, He is a Rebel.
什麼讓你…什麼讓你興奮？
What are your...What are your turn-ons?
米基·洛克
Mickey Rourke
一個能欣賞生活中更美好事物的男人  比如糖
a man who can appreciate the finer things in life, like sugar.
埃爾維的嗓音  功夫  派
Elvis' voice, kung fu, pie.
避開的？
Turnoffs?
避開
Turnoffs.
波斯人
Persians.
你有男人嗎？
Do you have a fella?
稍等一會兒再問我這個
Ask me that one a little bit later.
影院裏滿是座位  為什麼  為什麼坐我旁邊？
In a theater full of empty seats, why did you sit by me?
因為你看著像是個好人
Because you looked like a nice guy.
所以我不得不灑你一身爆米花
So I had to dump my popcorn all over you.
我來結賬  接下來去哪兒？
I'll get the check. Where to next?
我能偷看嗎？
Can I peek?
別偷看  眼睛閉好  好嗎？
Now don't peek. Keep your eyes shut, all right?
好了  我要開燈了
All right, I am turning the lights on.
好了  睜眼
Okay, open them.
哇  在這地方工作太好了
Wow, what a swell place to work!
對  挺酷的  我有鑰匙…
Yeah, it's pretty cool. I got the keys...
所以我就進來  看看漫畫書  放放音樂
so I just come in, you know, read comics, play music.
你在這裏工作很久了？
You worked here a long time?
哦  快四年了
Almost four years.
挺長時間了
That is a long time.
對  我知道  但也沒那麼糟
Yeah, I know, but it's not so bad.
我是說  我對大多數顧客很友善
I mean I'm pretty friendly with most of the customers.
所以我就晃晃  吹吹牛  讀讀漫畫書
So I just hang out, bullshit, read comic books.
你工資不少？
You get paid a lot?
不  那正是天堂的煩惱  不過…
No, that's where the trouble comes into paradise, but...
老闆是個挺好的人
The boss is a pretty nice guy.
他讓你時不時借點錢  如果有需要的話
He lets you borrow money from time to time, if you need it.
你想看看蜘蛛俠一號是什麼樣子嗎？
You want to see what Spiderman No. 1 looks like?
絕對的
You bet.
很棒的故事  很棒的角色  漂亮的圖畫
Just great stories, great characters, beautiful artwork.
看  這裏這個人  尼克…
See, in this one here, Nick
他為他的愛人弄到一個戒指
he's gotten this ring here for his sweetheart
他把它用鏈子掛在脖子上
and he wears it around his neck on a chain.
然後故事的後頭  他跟一個納粹雜種打了一架
And later on in the story, he gets in this fight with this Nazi bastard.
那德國鬼子抓住了鏈子
And the Kraut grabs hold of the chain.
戒指從船上掉了下去
Well, the ring goes overboard.
尼克  他潛到大海裏去拿
Nick, he dives into the ocean to get it.
是不是很酷？
Isn't that cool?
不要等到塵埃落定
怎麼了？你…
What is it? You...
你在哭？是因為我嗎？是我做了什麼嗎？
You're crying? What did I do? Did I do something?
你沒做什麼
You didn't do nothing.
是什麼事？
What is it?
我有事情得告訴你
I have something I got to tell you.
我不是碰巧在那家影院  我收了錢去的
I didn't just happen to be at that theater. I was paid to be there.
你收了錢去那裏  你是什麼人？
If you were paid to be there, what are you?
影院檢查員？
A theater-checker?
你受聘去檢查那些票房姑娘
You get paid to check upon the box-office girls
確保她們不會偷票房？
make sure they're not ripping the place off?
我不是影院檢查員  我是個應招女郎
I'm no theater-checker. I'm a call girl.
你是妓女？
You're a whore?
不  我是應招女郎  不一樣的  知道嗎
No! I'm a call girl, and there is a difference, you know!
好吧  我說了
Okay, here it goes.
你知道昨晚你帶我去的那個地方吧？
You know the place you took me to last night?
你工作的地方
The place you work.
"超級英雄出售"？
Heroes for Sale?
你有個老闆  對吧？
You got a boss, right?
對
Yeah.
好  他叫什麼名字？
Okay, what's his name?
蘭斯
Lance.
就是他
That's him.
他打電話給我工作的地方
He called the place where I work.
給你點了個女孩  他說他想讓你搞一炮
He ordered a girl for you. He said he wanted you to get laid.
說你不怎麼出門  那是你的生日什麼的
Said you didn't get out much, and it was your birthday and all.
他想要我裝成意外出現
He wanted me to act like I just showed up.
他怎麼知道你會在那家影院？
How did he know you were going to be at that theater?
我…我每年生日都去看電影  實際上…
I go to the movies every year on my birthday. In fact...
他這周給我打過電話
He called me this week
想搞清楚我會去看什麼生日電影
to find out what my birthday movie was going to be.
你沒瘋吧？
You're not mad?
沒有  老天
No, man.
我可以告訴你  那是我有生以來最棒的時候之一
I can't tell you that was one of the best times I ever had.
真的
It was.
你看  我就知道其中必有古怪
You know, I knew something must be rotten in Denmark.
你不可能那麼喜歡我
There's no way you could like me that much.
我可以告訴你  你脫掉衣服時我多麼如釋重負  你…
I can tell you how relieved I was when you took off your dress you...
你沒有掏出一根屌來
you didn't have a dick.
別他媽的對這事那麼淡定了
Stop being so fucking calm about all this!
去你屋裏看看  你電視上有張紙條
Go look in your house. There's a note on your TV.
只寫著"親愛的克拉倫斯"  因為我寫不下去了
It only says "Dear Clarence," because I couldn't write anymore.
所以我就寫："阿拉巴馬  坦白交代
So I just said, "Alabama, come clean.
"告訴他是怎麼回事  如果他叫你…
"Just tell him what's what. And if he tells you...
"回德拉科斯那裏去自己搞自己吧
"...to go back to Drexl and fuck yourself...
"那就回德拉科斯那裏去自己搞自己
"...then go back to Drexl and fuck yourself".
德拉科斯？什麼德拉科斯？
Drexl? What's a Drexl?
拜託閉嘴！我在坦白呢  好嗎？
Please shut up! I'm trying to come clean, okay?
我當應招女郎正好四天  你是我第三個客人
I've been a call girl for exactly four days and you are my third customer.
我要你知道  我不是次等品
I want you to know, that I am not damaged goods.
我不是他們在佛羅里達所說的"白人垃圾"
I'm not what they call in Florida, white trash!
我真的是個好人
I'm a really good person.
而且說到人際關係
And when it comes to relationships...
我是百分之百的…
I am one hundred percent.
I am one hundred percent
一夫一妻制
monogamous.
你會從一而終？
You stay with one guy?
正是  如果我跟你在一起  我就跟你
Exactly. If I'm with you, then I'm with you.
我不會想要別人
And I don't want anybody else.
現在  我得告訴你另一件事
Now, I got to tell you something else.
你說昨晚是你有生以來最棒的時候之一
When you said last night was one of the best times you've had...
你是指肉體上的嗎？
did you mean physically?
對對  但我說的是整個晚上  我是說…
Yeah, yeah. But I'm talking about the whole night. I mean I...
我從未跟哪個女孩像和你一起那麼多樂趣  我一輩子裏
I never had as much fun with a girl, as I had with you, my whole life.
是真的  我是說…
It's true. I mean...
你喜歡埃爾維斯  你喜歡詹尼斯
You like Elvis. You like Janis...
你喜歡功夫電影  你喜歡帕曲吉一家
you like kung fu movies. You like The Partridge Family....
其實  我不喜歡帕曲吉一家
Actually, I don't like The Partridge family.
那個是裝的
That was part of the act.
克拉倫斯
Clarence
我覺得說這話真的很傻…
And I feel really goofy saying this...
我只是認識你一個晚上
after only knowing you one night
而且我還是個應招女什麼的…
and me being a call girl and all....
但我想我愛你
But, I think I love you.
等一下
Wait a second.
瞧
Look
我一直試著保持正確處理這件事
I've been trying to keep this whole thing in perspective.
你剛才說你愛我  如果我說了我愛你  把警惕拋諸腦後…
You just said you loved me. If I say I love you, throw caution to the wind...
任憑喜從天降  而你其實是在說謊  我他媽就死定了
let the chips fall as they may, and you're lying, I'll fucking die.
我現在沒跟你說謊
I'm not lying to you.
而且我發誓從此刻以後…
And I swear from this moment forth...
我永遠不會再跟你說謊
I will never lie to you again.
噢  你好  沃利太太
Well, hello, Mrs. Worley.
你好嗎  沃利先生？
How do you do, Mr. Worley.
祝你一天好心情  沃利太太
Top of the morning to you, Mrs. Worley.
看球愉快哦  沃利先生
Bottom of the ninth, Mr. Worley.
對了  你今天見過你可愛的妻子了嗎？
By the way, have you seen your lovely wife today?
我那漂亮迷人性感的妻子 阿拉巴馬·沃利太太嗎？
My beautiful, charming, sexy wife Mrs. Alabama Worley?
怎麼？還有別的嗎  沃利先生？
Why? Are there any others, Mr. Worley?
不  我沒有  沒有
No, not for me, no.
- 不  不要  - 要  要
- No. No.  - Yes, yes.
（克拉倫斯）
請問
Excuse me.
你能不能稍微把溫度調低一點點？
Do you think you could turn down the heat just a teeny bit?
靠  我必須問你一個問題
Damn I gotta ask you a question.
德拉科斯是誰或是什麼？
Who and what is a Drexl?
- 噓  - 啊？
- Shush.  - Huh?
以前他是我的皮條客
He was my pimp.
你有個拉皮條的？
You had a pimp?
我以前是個應招女
I was a call girl.
應招女郎有拉皮條的
Call girls have pimps.
他是黑人嗎？
Was he black?
他覺得他是
He thinks he is.
他說過他媽媽是阿帕奇族  但我覺得他騙人的
He said his mama was an Apache but I suspect he's lying.
他人好嗎？
Is he nice?
我不會談論這麼深入的事情  不過…
I wouldn't go so far as to say that, but...
他對待我相當得體
He treated me pretty decent.
我只在那裏待了四天  有一天他有一點兇
I was only there for four days. He got a little bit rough the other day.
- 你是說  對你？  - 不  對我的朋友艾琳
- What do you mean? With you? - No, with my friend Ilene.
他怎麼對艾琳？
What did he do to Ilene?
耳光扇得她有點轉圈  踢她肚子  有點…
Slapped her around a little bit. Kicked her in the stomach. It was...
嚇人
scary.
這媽逼的真是漂亮
This motherfucker sounds beautiful.
你怎麼會弄到跟那種狗娘養的混呢？
What did you do to end up with a son of a bitch like that?
（汽車旅館）
你們他媽的說什麼呢？
What are you motherfucker talking about?
弗洛伊德說 他不舔屄了
Floyd say he don't be eating pussy.
德拉科斯
Drexl
去  哪個黑鬼說他不舔屄 就是他媽的撒謊
any nigger says he don't eat pussy's lying his ass off.
我聽說了
I heard that.
等一下  大D  你是說你舔屄？
Hold on a second. Big D., you saying you eat pussy?
對  媽逼的  我啥都舔
Yeah, motherfucker, I eat everthing.
我舔屄  我舔小花蕾  我他媽什麼的都舔
I eat the pussy, I eat the bud. I eat every fucking thing.
如果我真的舔了屄
If I ever did eat any pussy,
我是絕對不會去舔的  明白？
I would never eat any pussy, right?
但如果我真的舔了
But if I did eat some pussy...
我打死也不會告訴哪個哥們的  但是…
I sure as hell wouldn't tell no goddamn body. But...
我會他媽逼的羞愧得很  老兄
I'd be ashamed as a motherfucker, man.
靠  黑鬼  你多抽些大麻…
Shit, nigger, you smoke enough Sherm...
你這榆木疙瘩就會他媽的做很多事
your dumb ass would do a lot of motherfucking things.
你就會在那裏吸老黑的屌
You'd be up in there suckin' niggers' dicks!
靠  操你們這幫混蛋
No, man. Fuck you guys, man.
你們真他媽完蛋了  曉得不？
You guys are fucked up, all right?
喂  等等  跟你他媽鬧著玩呢
Hey. Wait a second. We's just fucking with you.
其實  我準備給你展示一下我的意思  做個示範
In fact, I'm going to show you what I mean with a little demonstration.
把那燒火棍扔過來
Toss me the burner.
好了  看好了
All right, dig this.
把它…當作雜誌插頁上的騷貨
Pretend it's that fine centerfold bitch.
知道我的意思吧？
You know what I'm saying?
而你就是你
And you are you.
- 親  你去哪兒？  - 衛生間
- Honey, where you going? - Bathroom.
多麼孤單  多麼孤單
So lonely...
多麼孤單  我要死了…
So lonely...I could die...
好吧  你能這麼過下去嗎？
Well, can you live with it?
什麼？
What?
我說你能這麼過下去嗎？
I said can you live with it?
怎麼過下去？
Live with what?
那個狗娘養的四處晃蕩  跟你呼吸著一樣的空氣
That son of a bitch walking around breathing the same air as you.
每天逍遙法外
Getting away with it every day.
你內心為此不安？
Are you haunted?
對
Yeah.
你想要不再為此不安？
You want to get un-haunted?
哦  是的
Oh, yeah.
哦  要我就殺了他
Well, I'd kill him.
給他臉上一槍  像條狗一樣放倒他
Shoot him in the face. Put him down like a dog.
我不敢相信你跟我說這話
I can't believe what you're telling me.
沒有  我只是在說我會怎麼做
I'm not saying nothing. I's just saying what I'd do.
你會那麼做？
You'd do that?
那狗日的不配活著
The fuck don't deserve to live.
瞧  他是在困擾我  你知道  我是說…
Look, he's haunting me, you know. I mean...
我是想殺了他  但我不想在監獄度過餘生
I do want to kill him, but I don't want to spend the rest of my life in jail.
嘿  夥計  我不怪你
Hey man, I don't blame you.
- 只要我能逃脫…  - 逃脫？
- If I thought I'd get away with it....  - Get away with it?
殺人是困難的
Killing is the hard part.
逃脫嗎？這個簡單
Getting away with it, that's easy.
你以為警察會他媽在意一個皮條客？
You think a cop gives a fuck about a pimp?
聽著  世上每個皮條客都該挨槍子兒
Listen. Every pimp in the world could get shot.
兩槍崩他媽的後腦勺上
Two in the back of the fucking head.
警察會開趴慶祝  老兄
Cops would throw a party, man.
只要你不是在犯罪現場被抓
As long as you're not at the scene of the crime...
手裏拿著冒煙的槍
with a smoking gun in your hand,
你就能逃脫處罰
you'll get away with it.
克拉倫斯  我喜歡你
Clarence, I like you.
向來如此  以後也會
Always have, always will.
芭瑪
'Bama.
你要去哪兒？
Where you going?
我要你寫下你以前的地址
I need you to write down your former address.
為什麼？
Why?
這樣我能去拿你的東西  就這樣
So I can go over there and pick up your stuff, that's why.
哦  寶貝  算了  克拉倫斯
Oh, baby, come on, Clarence.
我只想從那裏消失
I just want to disappear from there.
你看
Look
芭瑪  我知道你嚇得要死  但我不怕那個他媽的雜碎
Bama, I know this scares the shit out of you, but I'm not scared of that motherfucker.
他完全夠不著你  他絕對威脅不了你
You are completely out of his reach. He poses absolutely no threat to you.
如果他不在乎  他的確不在乎
If he...If he doesn't matter which he doesn't...
那你丟棄你全部家當就太傻了  就這樣
then it just seems silly you lose all your things now. That's all.
聽著
Listen.
你不瞭解他
You don't know him.
不  你不瞭解我
No, you don't know me.
不瞭解面對這種事的我
Not when it comes to shit like this.
我需要去做
I need to do this.
我只是…我想要你知道你可以信得過我保護你
I just...I want you to know that you can count on me to protect you.
來吧  請你寫下來
Come on, please just write it down.
這不是好主意
This isn't a good idea.
我告訴你  沒事的
I'm telling you, it'll be fine.
我進去就出來
I'll be in and out of there.
- 要小心  - 我會的
- Be careful. - I will.
我愛你
I love you.
我也愛你
I love you, too.
蒙特卡洛東街 447
你找什麼？
You want something?
對  你是德拉科斯？
Yeah, you Drexl?
不  老兄  我是馬蒂
No man, I'm Marty.
我想跟德拉科斯談談
Well, I want to talk to Drexl.
你想跟他談他媽的什麼？
Well, what the fuck you want to talk to him about?
有關阿拉巴馬的
It's about Alabama.
他在問阿拉巴馬的事
He was asking about Alabama.
那婊子在他媽哪裏？
Where the fuck is that bitch?
她跟我在一起
She's with me.
你他媽是誰？
Who the fuck are you?
我是她丈夫
I'm her husband.
哦  那咱倆還真是特別有關聯呢
Well, that makes us practically related.
坐下吧  伙子
Have a seat, boy.
來吃個蛋卷  我們這裏啥都有…
Have an egg roll. We got everything here...
從"小眼約耳"到"我他媽不知道是啥"
from "Little-Eye Joel" to "Damned if I know".
不  謝了
No, thanks.
不  謝了？
No, thanks?
你什麼意思？
What that mean?
我想你是嚇得不敢吃吧
I think you're too scared to be eating.
你看…
Now, see....
我們坐在這裏  準備談判
We're sitting down here, ready to negotiate.
而你已經啥都放棄了
And you've already given up your shit.
對你來說我仍然是個謎團
I'm still a mystery to you.
但我完全知道你這小白臉是從哪兒來的
But I know exactly where your white ass is coming from.
看  如果我問你要不要吃點晚飯…
See if I ask you if you want some dinner
然後你拿起一個蛋卷大嚼…
and you grab an egg roll start to chew...
我會說：這狗逼樣的  他做事情好像一點不在乎
I say, this motherfucker, he's acting like he ain't got a care in the world.
誰知道呢？也許他真就那麼猛
And who knows? Maybe he don't.
也許這傻子就是…一個他媽的狠人
Maybe this fool is such a bad motherfucker...
他啥球事情也不擔心  他就是坐下來…
he don't have to worry about nothing. He just sits down...
看他媽的我的電視
and watches my motherfucking TV.
明白嗎？
See?
而你連坐都沒坐下來
You haven't even sat down yet.
還有那個電視  你走進一個房間…
And that TV over there, since you've been in a room...
有個女人胸部晃來晃去的
has a woman with her breast just hanging out.
你都沒費心看上一眼
Well, you haven't even bothered to look.
你就光盯著我
You just been clocking me.
我知道我挺漂亮
Now, I know I'm pretty.
可我沒有一對奶子漂亮
But I ain't as pretty as a couple of titties.
這孩子挺暴躁
This child be fierce.
我沒吃  是因為我不餓
I'm not eating because I'm not hungry.
我沒坐下  是因為我不會逗留
I'm not sitting because I'm not staying.
我沒有看那電影  是因為我七年前就看過了
I'm not looking at the movie because I've already seen it seven years ago.
那是《造物主》
It is The Mack.
馬克斯·朱利安  卡羅爾·斯彼得  還有理查德·普賴爾
Max Julian, Carol Speed and Richard Pryor.
我不怕你  我只是不喜歡你
I'm not scared of you. I just don't like you.
我剛放下的是贖身錢  阿拉巴馬已經奔更好的前程去了
That I put right there is payoff money. Alabama is moving on to greener pastures.
所以我們不是在談判  我不喜歡討價還價
So we're not negotiating, I don't like to barter.
我剛放下的是我一點心意
That I put right there is for my peace of mind.
我的心意就那麼多  多一分錢沒有
My peace of mind is worth that much. Not one penny more.
是空的
It's empty.
馬蒂
Marty
知道我們這位是誰嗎？
you know what we got here?
這是他媽的周潤發啊
A motherfucking Charlie Bronson.
"小馬哥？"
"Mr. Majestyk?"
看好了  發哥
Look here, Charlie.
這些廢話毫無必要
None of this bullshit is necessary.
我根本沒管著阿拉巴馬
I don't got no hold over Alabama.
我不過是給一個女孩幫把手
I was just trying to lend a girl a helping hand.
我操
Fuck!
來啊  跟我鬥！
Come on, fuck with me!
你自找的
That's what you get.
你搞我  白小子
You fuck with me, white-boy!
看好了  你%#&#！
Look at this! You fond of my motherfucking freaks?
狗屎  你媽了個逼的
Shit! You motherfucker!
你他媽瘋了
Your ass fucking crazy!
你一定以為今天有利白人小子
You must have thought it was white-boy day.
今天不利白人小子  對吧？
It ain't white-boy day, is it?
對  哥們  不利白人小子
No man, it ain't white-boy day.
靠  夥計  你不能再蹦躂了
Shit man, you don't fucked up again.
喔喔喔
Well, well, well.
瞧瞧這是什麼
Look what we got here.
克拉倫斯·沃利？
Clarence Worley?
聽著很像是個黑鬼名字
It sounds almost like a nigger name.
我知道你住哪裏了
And I know where you live.
160大街 4900
4900, 160th Street...
48號公寓
Apartment 48.
我可以賭一百萬  阿拉巴馬也在同一個地方
And I would make a million-dollar bet, that Alabama is at the same address.
馬蒂  取車  去抓她  把那蠢婊子帶回來
Marty, take the car, go get her. Bring her dumb ass back here.
我要留著這情哥哥娛樂一下
I think I'll keep lover boy here entertained.
喂  馬蒂
Hey, Marty!
你他媽幹嘛？
What the fuck are you doing?
- 我找不到外衣了  -  去看看衣服籃子裏
- I can't find my jacket! - Go look in the fucking hamper.
你
You!
拿個袋子裝上阿拉巴馬的東西
Get a bag and put Alabama's things in it.
你他媽想挨槍子？
You want to get fucking shot?
拿個袋子裝上阿拉巴馬的東西
Get a bag and put Alabama's things in it!
我剛剛幫了你他媽一輩子最大的忙
I just did you the biggest fucking favor of your life!
睜開眼睛
Open your eyes.
我說了睜開你他媽的眼睛
I said open your fucking eyes!
你以為這他媽的挺好玩  對吧？
You thought it was pretty fucking funny. Didn't you?
我操你這坨屎
Fuck you! You piece of shit!
別他媽的動
Don't fucking move!
我很自私  我知道我自私  不過…
I was selfish. I know I was selfish. l was, but...
我懷著你的孩子  寶貝
I was carrying your child, babe.
我殺了他
I killed him.
來個漢堡什麼的？我他媽的餓死了
Want a hamburger or something? I'm fucking starving to death.
這是開玩笑嗎？
Is this a joke?
不開玩笑
No joke.
這是我這輩子吃過最他媽好吃的漢堡
That was the best god damn fucking hamburger I ever had in my entier life.
我從沒嘗過這麼好吃的漢堡
I've never had a hamburger taste this good.
來吃點  你會感覺好些
Come on, eat something, you'll feel better.
你哭他媽什麼勁？
What the fuck you crying for?
老天爺  他不值得你流一滴眼淚
I mean Chris, he's not worth one of your tears.
你寧願是我死嗎？
Would you rather it have been me?
是這意思嗎？
Is that it?
那是你想要的嗎？我說  你是不是愛他？
Is that what you want? I mean, do you love him?
你愛他嗎？
Do you love him?
我說你他媽是不是愛他？
I said, do you fucking love him?
- 我覺得你所做的…  - 怎樣？
- I think what you did was... - What?
- I think what you did... - What?
真是浪漫
was so romantic.
寶貝  你流血了
Oh, baby, you're bleeding.
我把你的東西拿來了
I got your things right here.
乾淨衣服
Clean clothes.
我愛你
I love you.
老天在上
There is a God.
這不是我的衣服
These aren't my clothes.
隆美爾  你去哪兒？過來夥計  上車
Rommel, where are you? Come here, come on boy, get in here.
快上車  上車  來
Get in here now. Get in here. Come on.
早上好  爸爸
Good morning, Daddy.
喂  隆美爾
Hey, Rommel.
好久不見
Long time no see, huh?
哦  夥計  好夥計
Oh, yeah, boy, good boy.
你一定要原諒這地方
Now you're going to have to excuse the place.
我最近這段時間沒有接待過…
I haven't been exactly doing a lot of entertaining...
太多人來
of company as of late.
抱歉我看起來有點緊張  但是…
I'm sorry if I seem a little tense. But..
在這個世界上  今早你是我最沒想到會見到的人
you're the last person in the world, that I expected to see this morning.
沒事的  爸爸  我自帶這屬性
Well, that's okay, Daddy, I tend to have that effect on people.
你這裏有什麼喝的沒有？我渴死了
You got anything to drink around here? I'm dying of thirst.
哦  應該有
Now there should be,
應該有一罐七喜在裏面
there should be a Seven-Up in there.
有沒有更烈的？
Anything stronger?
應該沒有
Probably not.
啤酒  你能喝啤酒  對吧？
Beer. You can drink beer, can't you?
我可以  但我不喝
I can, but I don't.
差不多都是我曾經吃過的
That's about all I ever eat.
抱歉了
Excuse me.
你好  你好  你好
Hello, hello, hello.
我是他父親
I'm his father.
- 你好？  - 沒關係  我是他妻子
- How are you?  - Well that's all right. I'm his wife,
阿拉巴馬·沃利  很高興認識你
Alabama Worley. Pleased to meet you.
我們結婚了
We got married.
愛  你當個好人去給我們買點啤酒如何？
Lover, why don't you be a sport and go get us some beer?
你要啤酒嗎？
You want some beer?
如果你要的話  這裏應該有  對吧？
I mean if you want some, it'll be here. All right?
附近酒類商店在哪裏？
Where is a liquor store around here?
54街有個派對商店
There is a party store down 54th Street.
拿個六瓶裝進口的
Get a six-pack of something imported.
很難跟你說哪個牌子  不同地方賣的不一樣
Hard to tell you what to get. Different places have different things.
給  這應該夠了  好嗎？
Here, that should cover it, okee-dokee?
好的好的  可以可以
Okee-dokee, Doggy Daddy.
她不是你這一輩子見過該死的最甜美的東西嗎？
Ain't she the sweetest goddamn thing you ever saw in your whole life?
我是說  她簡直四級火辣什麼的
I mean, is she a four-alarm fire, or what?
她看著很不錯
She seems very nice.
不錯？
Nice?
爸  "不錯"這詞不對  我說這女孩就是水蜜桃
Daddy, "nice" is not the word. I mean this girl, she's a peach, You know.
對  她味道也像水蜜桃
Yes, she even tastes like a peach.
你看得出我愛她  對嗎？
You can tell I'm in love with her, can't you?
不  等等  我有話說
No, wait. I gotta talk.
坐下  閉嘴
Sit down! Shut up!
你他媽讓我頭大
You give me a fucking headache.
我是說  你太像你媽了  我不敢相信
I mean. You are so much like your mother, I can't believe it.
你他媽的就是你媽  徹頭徹尾
You are your fucking mother, through and through.
我三年沒聽到你消息
I haven't heard from you in three years.
你突然之間就出現  大早上的八點鐘
You show up all of a sudden, at 8:00 in the morning...
你走進來  像台該死的推土機
you walk in here like a goddamned bulldozer.
別會錯意  我愛你  我高興看見你
Now don't get me wrong. I love you, I'm glad to see you.
但要慢慢來  老兄
But slow it down, man.
好嗎？
All right?
好了
Now.
你什麼時候結的婚？
When did you get married?
爸…
Well, Daddy....
我…我惹上他媽的大麻煩了
I'm in...I'm in big fucking trouble.
我…我真的需要你幫忙
I just...I really need your help.
不不不  別說了
No, no, stop talking.
- 你要我做什麼？  - 什麼？
- What do you want from me?  - What?
你要我做什麼？
What do you want from me?
別再像個小孩子一樣了
Stop acting like an infant!
你來是因為你要我幫你做什麼  我…
You're here because you want me to help you in someway. I...
你要我做什麼？你需要錢？
What do you need from me? You need money?
不
No.
你還有朋友在警察部門嗎？
You still have friends on the force?
有  我還有朋友在警察部門
Yes, I still have friends on the force.
那你能不能去搞清楚 他們知不知道我們的事？
Well then could you just find out if they know anything about us?
我認為他們屁也不知道  但我不想認為  我要確定
I don't think they know shit. But I don't wanna think, I want to know for sure.
我看你能辦到  對嗎？
I mean you can do that. Right?
你為什麼認為我能辦到？
What makes you think I could do that?
因為你當過警察
Because you were a cop.
但你為什麼認為我會去做？
But what makes you think that I would do that?
因為我是你兒子
Because I'm your son.
哦  你是我兒子
Oh, you're my son.
哦  你全都計劃好了  是不是？
Oh, you got it all worked out, don't you?
哦  行啊
Oh, yeah.
聽著  該死  我從沒要求過你一件事
Look. I mean, goddamn, I've never asked you for a goddamn thing.
老天他媽的在上  媽媽跟你離婚後
Jesus fucking Christ! After Mom divorced you...
我曾求過你什麼事嗎？
did I ever ask you for anything?
不  我沒有
No. I didn't.
當我會有一年半到兩年見不到你時
When I wouldn't see you for one and a half to two years...
我曾跟你吐過槽嗎？
did I ever get into your shit about it?
還有你他媽的喝醉的那些時候
and that whole fucking time you were drunk,
我有沒有生氣指責過你？
did I ever get mad point my finger to you?
不  我從來沒有  別人都有過  但我沒有
No! I never did. Everybody else did, but I didn't!
瞧  我只是需要幫助
Now look, I just need help
你他媽的能幫我  知道嗎？
and you can fucking help me. All right?
我基本上是個資源多的人
Now, I'm basically a resourceful guy.
如果不是我真的需要  我也不會問你
If I didn't really need it, I wouldn't ask.
如果你要說不  那好吧
I mean, if you want to say no, then fine.
算了  別操心了  沒問題  我走  好嗎？
Forget it, don't worry about it. No problem, I'm gone, all right?
童貞聖母回來了
The Virgin is back!
謝天謝地  我能吃下一匹馬…
Thank God. I could eat a horse.
我沒給你買雞
I didn't get you any chicken.
怎麼回事？
Well, how come?
親  現在太早了  只是九點鐘
Honey, it's too early in the morning. It's only 9:00.
狗娘養的
Son of a bitch!
迪克·裏奇  迪克·裏奇！
Dick Richie! Dick Richie!
是我  我是我
That's me, I'm me.
進來
Come inside.
好
Okay.
坐  坐坐坐
Sit. Sit, sit.
好
Now.
你要讀的是壞人當中的一個
The part you'll be reading is one of the bad guys.
有布萊恩和馬蒂
There's Brian and Marty.
誰？
Who?
有問題嗎？
Is there a problem?
沒有  沒有
No. No.
彼得·佈雷克已經選上布萊恩的角色
Peter Breck has been cast in the part of Brian.
所以你要讀馬蒂的角色
So, you'll be reading for the role of Marty.
這場戲裏  你倆在車上  比爾·沙特納掛在引擎蓋上
In this scene, you're both in a car, and Bill Shatner's hanging on the hood.
你想要做的  就是把他甩掉
What you want to do is get him off.
好的  我是馬蒂
All right, I'm Marty.
- 準備好了？  - 對
- Ready? - Yeah.
我在開車
I'm driving.
好了
Okay.
"他他媽的從哪兒來的？"
"Where the fuck did he come from?"
"我不知道  他變魔術一樣出現了"
"I don't know, he just appeared like magic".
"別光坐在那裏  開槍打他"
"Well, don't just sit there, shoot him!"
"搞掂他"
"Get him!"
謝謝  裏奇先生
Thank you, Mr. Richie.
我很佩服  你是個很不錯的演員
I'm very impressed. You're a very fine actor.
謝謝你
Thank you.
我們會通知你的
We'll let you know.
好的
Okay.
- 好  一隻手  - 一隻手  來吧
- Okay, one-handed. - One hand. Here we go.
好  試試另一隻
Good, try on the other one there.
火車來了
Here comes the train.
好了  他們什麼也沒發現
Well, they found nothing.
實際上  他們認為是毒品案
In fact, they think it's drug related.
毒品案？為什麼是毒品案？
Drug related? Why drug related?
哦  顯然德拉科斯插了一腳那東西
Well, apparently Drexl had his big toe stuck in that shit.
真的？
Really?
德拉科斯跟一個叫布魯·盧·博伊爾的人有關聯
Drexl had an association with a fellow named Blue Lou Boyle.
- 這名字你有印象嗎？  - 沒有
- Name mean anything to you? - No.
哦  如果你不在他的圈子混  就沒有理由知道
Well, if you don't hang around his circle, no reason it should.
他是誰？
Who is he?
黑幫分子  毒販  一個你不想招惹的人
Gangster, drug dealer. Somebody that you don't want him on your ass.
聽著  克拉倫斯
Now look, Clarence
我打聽到這個他媽的德拉科斯越多的事
the more I hear about this Drexl fucker...
我就越覺得你做了件好事
the more I think you did the right thing.
這人不單單是個野小子
This guy was not just some wild flake.
我先前就試圖跟你說了  這人就像是條瘋狗
That's what I was trying to tell you before. The guy was like a mad dog.
那麼  警察  他們沒覺得…他們沒在追我們？
So, the cops, they don't think.... They're not after us?
沒有  除非他們聽到更多消息
No. Until they hear something better.
他們只會假設德拉科斯跟布魯·盧鬧翻了
They will just assume Drexl had a falling out with Blue Lou.
一旦你離開這裏  我都不會擔心
And once you leave town, I wouldn't even worry about it.
謝謝  多謝了  老爸  你真幫我過了難關
Thanks, thanks a lot, Daddy. You really came through for me.
我有些錢可以給你
I got some money I could give you.
不  留著  留著吧
No, keep it. Keep it.
那麼  兒子
Well now, son.
我要你知道…
I want you to know that...
我希望你跟阿拉巴馬一切順利
I hope everything works out with you and Alabama.
我喜歡她
I like her.
我覺得你們會是很可愛的一對
And I think you make a real cute couple.
是的  那個  你別惹麻煩
Yeah, well, you stay out of trouble.
記住你現在…你有個妻子要考慮了
Remember you got a...you got a wife to think about now.
別再四處亂搞
Quit fucking around.
兒子
Son...
我愛你
I love you.
好了
All right.
這是我朋友迪克·裏奇 在好萊塢的號碼和地址
This is my friend Dick Richie's number and address in Hollywood.
我們會去那裏  跟我聯繫
That's where we'll be. Get in touch with me.
好的
All right.
來吧  阿拉巴馬  我們走  跟老爸吻別
Come on, Alabama. We're taking off. Kiss Pops goodbye.
再見  爸爸  希望很快再見你
'Bye, Daddy. Hope to see you again soon.
喂 喂
Hey, hey!
這是搞啥子？
What kind of smackaroo is that?
我會從好萊塢給你寄張明信片
I'll send you a postcard from Hollywood.
阿拉巴馬 阿拉巴馬
Alabama. Alabama.
是  先生？
Yes, sir?
替我照顧那個人
Take care of that one for me.
別擔心  爸爸  我會盯緊他的
Don't worry, Daddy. I'll keep him on a short leash.
夕陽慢慢西下  我們就此告辭
As the sun sets slowly in the west. We bid you a fine farewell.
- 再見  爸爸  - 再見  芭瑪
- Bye Daddy  - Bye, Bama
狗娘養的說得對  她味道像桃子
Son of a bitch was right. She tastes like a peach.
來吧  隆美爾
Come on, Rommel.
來吧夥計
Come on boy.
你好
Hello.
你好  寶貝
Hello, baby!
克拉倫斯？
Clarence?
猜對了
You got it!
克拉倫斯  聽到你聲音太好了  有什麼事？
Clarence, it's great to hear from you, what's going on?
你很快會見到我
Well, you're going to be seeing me shortly.
你來洛城了  什麼時候？
You're coming to LA! When?
明天
Tomorrow.
那封信背後還有故事呢  等見了你我再告訴你
There's a story behind the letter. I'll tell you when I see you.
對了  我不是一個人  我帶著我可愛的妻子
By the way, I won't be alone. I'm bringing my lovely wife.
你他媽不是吧  克拉倫斯  你結婚了？
Get the fuck out of here. Clarence, you got married?
我是已婚男人了  哥們
I'm a married man, buddy.
你想跟我的另一半打個招呼嗎？來
You want to say hello to my better half? Come here.
嗨  迪克  我是阿拉巴馬·沃利
Hi, Dick. This is Alabama Worley.
你好嗎  阿拉巴馬·沃利？
How you doing, Alabama Worley?
克拉倫斯跟我說過你  他說你是他最好的朋友
Clarence told me about you. He said you're his best friend.
- 我想也就是說你也是我最好的朋友了  - 告訴他我們得走了
- I guess that makes you my best friend too. - Tell him we got to go.
克拉倫斯說我們得走了
Clarence says we got to go.
等等  我能跟克拉倫斯說話嗎？
Wait, can I speak to Clarence, please?
問問他收到那封信沒有
Ask him if he got the letter.
你收到那封信沒有？
Did you get the letter?
什麼信？
What letter?
- 什麼信？  - 好幾封信
- What letter?  - Letters.
我什麼信也沒收到過
I didn't get any letter.
他還沒去拿郵件？
Has he gotten his mail yet?
- 你沒去收郵件嗎？  - 沒有  我的室友弗洛伊德…
- Have you gotten your mail yet? - No, my roommate, Floyd....
- 他查看過沒有？  - 你查看過沒有？
- Has he looked through it? - Have you looked through it?
沒有
Nap
告訴他去查看一下
Tell him to go look through it.
去查看一下
Go and look through it.
等等等等  我能不能跟克拉倫斯說話？
Wait, wait, wait. Can I speak to Clarence, please?
他想跟你說
He wants to talk to you.
我們沒時間了  告訴他我們得走了
We have no time. Tell him we got to go.
- 我們沒時間了  - 告訴他看那封信
- We have no time. - Tell him, "Read the letter".
看那封信
Just read the letter.
告訴他我愛他  告訴他到了明天…
Tell him I love him. Tell him as of tomorrow.
他愛你  親  拿著這個
He loves you. Honey, hold this.
- 好  告訴他到了明天  - 到了明天…
- All right, tell him as of tomorrow  - As of tomorrow...
- 他所有的金錢問題…  - 你所有的金錢問題都解決了
- all of his money problem  - all your money problems gonna be over.
喂？什麼金錢問題？
Hello? What money problems?
再見
Bye-bye.
喂  喂
Hello? Hello?
弗洛伊德
Floyd!
弗洛伊德  你用掉了最後一張廁紙
Floyd, you used up the last piece of toilet paper.
喂  隆美爾
Hey! Rommel!
喂  過來  隆美爾
Hey, come here! Rommel!
弗蘭基
Frankie.
叫盧卡出去做那個事
Tell Luca to go outside and do you know what.
你知道我是誰嗎？沃利先生？
Do you know who I am, Mr. Worley?
我放棄  你是誰？
I give up. Who are you?
反基督者
The anti-Christ.
你弄得我心情如同血海深仇
You got me in a vendetta kind of mood.
你可以告訴天堂的天使們
You can tell the angels in heaven...
你從未見過魔鬼如此異常的表現
you never saw evil so singularly personified...
就像你面前這個殺死你的男人那樣
as you did in the face of the man who killed you.
我的名字是文森特·科卡蒂  我是布魯·盧·博伊爾先生的軍師
My name is Vincent Coccotti. I work as counsel for Mr. Blue Lou Boyle.
就是被你兒子偷了的那個人
The man your son stole from.
我聽說你曾當過警察  所以我能假設你以前聽說過我們
I hear you were once a cop, so I can assume you have heard of us before.
我說得對嗎？
Am I correct?
我聽說過布魯·盧·博伊爾
I've heard of Blue Lou Boyle.
我很高興
I'm glad.
希望這能澄清你問自己的 "我是不是腦子進屎了"這個問題
Hopefully that will clear up the how-full-of-shit-am-I question you been asking yourself.
我們要來一場小小的問與答
We're going to have a little Q and A.
鑒於說話有過於累贅的風險  請你…
And at the risk of sounding redundant, please...
老老實實回答
make your answers genuine.
來一支契斯特菲爾德嗎？
Want a Chesterfield?
不
No.
我自己有個兒子  大概是你兒子的年齡
I have a son of my own, about your boy's age.
我能想像這對你一定是有多麼痛苦  但是…
I can imagine how painful this must be for you. But...
克拉倫斯
Clarence...
還有他那婊子女友  他們自找的這些
and his bitch of a girlfriend, brought this all on themselves.
我懇求你  不要沿他們的老路走下去
I implore you not to go down that road with them.
你總是能得到寬慰的  事實上  你永遠沒得選
You could always take comfort, in the fact you never had a choice.
瞧  可以的話我願意幫你  但我…
Look, I'd like to help you if I could, but I...
沒見過克拉倫斯
haven't seen Clarence.
你看見這個了嗎？
You see that?
不聰明  對吧？鼻子挨一拳
Unsmart, doesn't it? To get slammed in the nose.
把你搞慘了
Fucks you all up.
你遭受那一股疼痛 穿擊過你的大腦
You get the pain shooting through your brain...
你的眼裏全是淚水
your eyes fill up with water.
一點都不好玩
It's not any kind of fun.
但是  我要給你提的條件
But, what I have to offer you,
會是蠻好的條件
that's as good as it's going to get.
而且不會再有那麼好了
And it won't ever get that good again.
我們跟你鄰居談過
We talked to your neighbors.
他們見過一輛凱迪拉克
They saw a Cadillac.
紫色凱迪拉克
Purple Cadillac.
克拉倫斯的紫色凱迪拉克
Clarence's purple Cadillac
昨天停在你的拖車前
parked in front of your trailer yesterday.
沃利先生
Mr. Worley.
你見過你兒子嗎？
Have you seen your son?
我見過他
I've seen him.
我不能確定他跟你說了多少  所以…
I can't be sure of how much what he told you. So...
有這種可能  你對此事還蒙在鼓裏
In the chance you're in the dark about some of this...
我來敲敲邊鼓
let me shed some light.
你兒子帶在身邊的那個妓女
That whore your boy hangs around with....
給她拉皮條的  是我一個合作者
Her pimp is an associate of mine.
我是說  這個拉皮條的  在其它方面為我工作
I mean this pimp in other affairs he works for me...
…做遞送  很顯然…
in a courier capacity. Well, apparently...
那骯髒的小妓女  發現我們要做一單生意
that dirty little whore found out we were going to do some business...
以為你兒子那個牛仔  帶著他的噴火器
because your son, the cowboy and his flame
走進那房間亂射個不停
came into the room blazing and didn't stop
直到他們確定人人都死了
until they were pretty sure everybody was dead.
你在說什麼？
What are you talking about?
我在說一場屠殺
I'm talking about a massacre.
他們偷走了我的毒品
They snatched my narcotics.
迅速逃離了那裏
Hightailed it out of there.
本來可以逃脫的
Would have got away with it.
但你兒子  是個豬頭…
But your son, fuckhead that he is...
把他的駕照 落在那死人的手裏了
left his driver's license in the dead guy's hand.
你看
You know.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
這是次要的
That's of minor importance.
重他媽的要的是  我相信你
What's of major fucking importance is that I believe you.
他們去哪兒了？
Where did they go?
度蜜月
On their honeymoon.
同一個問題問第二次  我會生氣
I'm getting angry asking the same question  a second time.
他們去哪兒了？
Where did they go?
他們沒告訴我  你先等一等聽我說
They didn't tell me. Now you just wait a minute and listen to me.
我有三年沒見克拉倫斯
I haven't seen Clarence in three years.
他昨天出現了
He shows up yesterday...
帶著一個年輕女孩  說他結婚了
with a young girl, saying that he got married.
他來要求…
He asked for
拿些現金  去度蜜月
some quick get cash to go on a honeymoon.
他問我他能不能借500美元
He asked me if he could borrow $500.
我覺得該幫幫他
I felt like helping him.
所以我給他寫了一張支票  我們早上去吃了早餐
So, I wrote him out a check. We went to breakfast in the morning.
那就是我最後一次見他
And that's the last I saw of him...
千真萬確
so help me God.
他們沒想過告訴我他們去哪兒
They never thought to tell me where they were going.
我也沒想起來問
And I never thought to ask.
維琴察先生[意大利語]
Vincenzo, sir.
什麼也沒有[意大利語]
There's nothing there.
這可不好[意大利語]
That's not good.
你看
You know.
西西里人…是說謊高手
Sicilians are great liars.
世界上最棒的
The best in the world.
我是西西里人
I'm Sicilian...
我父親是西西里說謊者裏頭的重量級冠軍
my father was the world heavyweight champion of Sicilian liars.
跟著他長大  我學會了肢體動作
From growing up with him, I learned the pantomime.
一個人說謊的時候  會做出17種不同的事情…
There are 17 different things a guy can do when he lies...
…來出賣他  男人有17種
to give himself away. A guy has got 17 pantomimes.
女人有20種  男人有17種  不過…
Woman has got 20. Guy has got 17. But...
如果你瞭解它們 就像你瞭解自己的臉一樣
if you know them, like you know your own face...
就能把所有測謊儀器打入地獄  現在…
they would beat lie detectors all to hell. Now...
我們現在做的  是一個"說和透露"的小遊戲
what we got here is a little game of "Show and Tell".
你不想透露給我任何東西  但你什麼都跟我說了
You don't want to show me nothing. But you're telling me everything.
我知道你知道他們在哪裏  所以…
I know you know where they are. So...
告訴我
tell me...
在我做出什麼 你躲不過去的傷害之前
before I do some damage you won't walk away from.
我現在 能不能來一支契斯特菲爾德？
Could I have one of those Chesterfields now?
當然
Sure.
你有沒有…
You got a...
火柴？不  等等
match? No wait.
別麻煩了  我有
Don't bother, I got one.
你是西西里人？
You're Sicilian, huh?
對  西西里人
Yeah, Sicilian.
你知道
You know....
我讀過很多書
I read a lot.
特別是有關歷史的事
Especially about things about history.
我發現這玩意兒讓人陶醉
I find that shit fascinating.
有這麼一個事實  我不知道你知不知道
Here's a fact, I don't know whether you know it or not.
西西里人  是黑鬼衍生出來的
Sicilians were spawned by niggers.
再說一次？
Come again?
這
It...
這是個事實  是的  你看…
It's a fact. Yeah. You see...
西西里人的血是黑色的  從他們的心臟泵出
Sicilians have black blood pumping through their hearts.
如果你不相信我  你可以去看看
And if you don't believe me, you can look it up.
好幾百好幾百年前  你看…
Hundreds and hundreds of years ago, you see...
摩爾人征服了西西里
the Moors conquered Sicily.
而摩爾人是黑鬼
And the Moors are niggers.
你看  老早以前
You see, way back then...
西西里人也跟北意大利的黃蜂一樣
Sicilians were like wops from northern Italy.
他們都有金髮藍眼
They all had blond hair and blue eyes.
但是呢…
But, well....
後來摩爾人移居過去  然後…
Then the Moors moved in there and...
他們改變了整個國家
they changed the whole country.
他們操了那麼多西西里女人
They did so much fucking with Sicilian women.
永遠改變了整個血統
That they changed the whole bloodline forever.
就這樣…
That is why...
金髮藍眼變成了…黑頭髮深色皮膚
blond hair, blue eyes became black hair and dark skin.
你知道  這讓我驚奇萬分
You know it's absolutely amazing to me...
想想  到了今天  幾百年之後…
to think to this day, hundreds of years later...
那個
that...
西西里人…
that Sicilians...
仍然帶著黑鬼的基因
still carry that nigger gene.
這東西…
Now this....
不  我在引述歷史
No, I am quoting history.
書上寫著  這是事實  寫著呢
It's written, it's a fact. It's written.
我愛這傢伙
I love this guy!
你的祖上是黑鬼
Your ancestors are niggers.
嘿
Hey!
對！對！
Yeah！Yeah!
你的曾曾曾曾祖母  操過一個黑鬼
And your great, great, great great grandmother fucked a nigger.
然後她有了一個半黑鬼孩子
And she had a half-nigger kid.
現在
Now...
這句是不是事實？告訴我
if that is a fact, tell me?
我在說謊嗎？
Am I lying?
因為你…
'Cause you...
你是部分紫茄子血統
you are part eggplant.
茄子茄子茄子
Egg! Egg! Egg!
你是哈密瓜
You are a cantaloupe.
幹得漂亮
That was beautiful.
我一直沒殺過人…
I haven't killed anybody...
從1984年以來
since 1984.
去這喜劇演員兒子的公寓
Go to this comedian's son's apartment.
找點能說明他去向的東西回來
Come back with something that tells me where that asshole went.
讓我能把這東西從我臉上抹掉
So I can wipe this egg off my face.
弗蘭科  怎麼了？
他說西西里人是黑鬼生的  唐·維琴察就殺了他
好好收拾這他媽的一家人
Fix this fucked-up family for good.
喂  老闆
Hey, Boss.
準備高興吧
Get ready to be happy.
"大家早上好  洛杉磯6:22  我是KBLU的戴維·佩裏"
'Morning, everybody. It's 6:22 here now in LA. I'm David Perry at KBLU.
喂
Hello?
弗洛伊德
Floyd.
能不能至少替我應一下門？
Can't you answer the door at least for me?
哦  老兄  我都沒聽見
Oh, man, I didn't even hear it.
喂
Hello?
你能不能時不時幫我一下？
Can't you help me every now and then?
好
Yes.
你打電話要的約會服務？
You call for a date?
我就知道是你
I knew it was you!
迪克  這是阿拉巴馬  阿拉巴馬  這是迪克
Dick, this is Alabama. Alabama, this is Dick.
很高興認識你
Nice to meet you!
- 你住這裏多久了？  - 嗨  我是阿拉巴馬
- How long have you lived here? - Hi, I'm Alabama.
- 你氣色不錯  - 這地方太棒了  真好
- You look good! - This is a great place. This is nice.
來  我餓極了  咱們去吃點東西
Come on, I'm starving. Let's get something to eat.
- 這是誰？  - 這是弗洛伊德
- Who's this? - This is Floyd.
咱們走  來吧
Let's go! Come on!
喂喂  我還沒跟你們說過呢
Hey. I didn't tell you guys yet?
那天我試鏡《胡克警長》非常成功
I had this really, really good audition for T.J. Hooker the other day.
你要去演《胡克警探》？
You're going to be on T.J. Hooker?
對  新版《胡克警探》
Yeah, the new T.J. Hooker.
希望好運
Knock on wood.
你見到柯克警監了？
You get to meet Captain Kirk?
你試鏡的時候是見不到他的
You don't get to meet him in the audition...
但是  如果我得到這個角色  希望  希望
but if I get the part, hope, hope....
- 那就太不可思議了  - 會很酷
- That would be amazing. - It'd be cool....
- 見到柯克警監  那會很酷  - 我知道
- Meeting Captain Kirk, that would be cool. - I know.
我們到了
Here we are.
蜜月套房
The honeymoon suite.
你真的陷入愛河了  對嗎？
You're really in love, aren't you?
我平生第一次
For the very first time in my life.
你知道那是什麼感覺嗎？
You know what that's like?
不知道
No.
不說
閉上你的嘴吧
Shut the fuck up.
你到底來洛杉磯幹什麼？
What are you doing in LA anyway, huh?
神聖之母瑪莉亞
Holy Mary, Mother of God.
這玩意兒不可能是真的
This shit can't be real.
- 它能讓你嗨  - 什麼？
- It'll get you high.  - What?
我說  它能讓你嗨
I said, it'll get you high.
嘿  咱們有有線電視
Hey, we got cable.
要紅酒嗎  親？
Want some wine, sweetheart?
好  一點就好  我不是太喜歡紅酒
Yeah, just a little bit, I'm not much of a wine gal.
這東西是他媽真的
That stuff is fucking real.
這他媽是真東西  克拉倫斯
This is fucking real, Clarence.
我當然希望如此
I certainly hope so.
你弄了好一大堆可卡因在這裏  老兄
You've got a hell of a lot of cocaine here, man.
我知道
I know.
你知不知道你這裏有他媽多少白粉？
Do you realize how much fucking coke you have?
不知道  告訴我
No, tell me.
我不知道  但他媽的相當多
I don't know, but it's a fucking lot!
這是德拉科斯的可卡因
This is DrexI's coke.
不  德拉科斯死了  你瞧  這是克拉倫斯的可卡因
No, Drexl is dead, you see. It's Clarence's coke.
克拉倫斯的  而且他想拿它幹什麼都可以
Clarence. And he can do whatever he wants with it.
克拉倫斯想的是賣掉它
What Clarence wants to do is to sell it.
然後我和芭瑪  我們跳上一架噴氣機
Then me and Bama here, we're gonna jump on a jet plane
餘生就花它過日子了
and spend the rest of our lives spending it.
你收到我的信沒？你給我牽了買家沒？
You got my letter? You lined up a buyer for me?
聽著  克拉倫斯  我不是可卡因先生  好嗎？
Listen, Clarence, I'm not Joe Cocaine, okay?
可是…你是個演員
But...you're an actor.
我聽說這幫好萊塢的人總是把它帶到片場
I hear these Hollywood guys get it delivered to the set all the time.
哦  他們這樣  好嗎？他們會
Well, they do. All right? They do.
也許有一天  等我開始當上成功的明星
Maybe one day, when I start being a successful actor...
我也會跟那些人一樣
I'll be like one of those guys.
但是到那天之前  我什麼也沒有  明白嗎？
But, until that day, I ain't got nothing. All right?
我沒有尿壺  也沒有窗戶可以把它扔出去
I don't have a pot to piss in, or a window to throw it out.
我只有他媽的弗洛伊德
All I got is fucking Floyd.
如果你要我每次賣一點  這事我能做
Now, if you want me to help you sell a little bit at a time that's all I can do.
不  不要每次賣一點
No. None of that little bit-at-a-time shit.
必須是全部一次出售  必須是這樣
It's got to be the whole enchilada in one shot. That's the way it gotta be.
克拉倫斯  你知不知道這有多難？
Clarence, do you have any idea how difficult that's gonna be?
你他媽在說什麼？
What the fuck you are talking about?
我把價值50萬美元的白粉按20萬賣
I'm offering $500,000 worth of white for $200,000.
你跟我說這樣很難？
You tell me that's gonna be difficult?
非常困難  這非常困難  你明白嗎？
Very difficult. That's very difficult, do you understand?
聽我說
Listen to me.
它難在你要賣給特定集團  你明白我在說什麼嗎？
It's difficult because you're selling to a particular group, do you understand what I'm talking about?
肥貓  大佬  能拿出20萬美元的人
Fat cats, big shots. Guys who can afford $200,000.
能用掉他媽滿滿一整箱可卡因的人
Guys who can use a whole fucking suitcase full of cocaine.
基本上  克拉倫斯  我不認識的那種人
Basically, Clarence, guys I don't know.
你不認識的那種人  更重要的是  他們也不認識你
And guys you don't know. And more importantly, they don't know you.
拜託  迪克
Come on, Dick.
好吧  克拉倫斯
Okay, Clarence.
聽好
Listen.
我認識一個人…
There's one guy that I know...
能幫上你的忙  克拉倫斯  但是…
that can help you out, Clarence, but...
我什麼也不能跟你擔保
I'm not guaranteeing you anything.
他是一線的？
Is he big-league?
不  他不是一線的  好嗎？
No. He's not big-league. Okay?
但他給一個大電影製作人當助理  那人叫李·多諾維茨
But he works as an assistant to a very big movie producer named Lee Donowitz.
李·多諾維茨負擔得起…
Lee Donowitz could afford...
也能用得上20萬美元的可卡因
and can use, $200,000-worth of coke.
就這個  這就是你能得到的
Being that that's what you have.
好  你告訴過他什麼？
All right, so what did you tell him?
你他媽指望我跟他說什麼？
What the fuck do you expect me to tell him?
我是說  我又不知道哪些話是胡扯哪些又不是
I mean I didn't know what the hell was bullshit and what wasn't.
另外  弗洛伊德把那封信的第二頁當煙抽了  懂嗎？
And besides, Floyd smoked the second page of the letter. Okay?
那個演藝階級的人叫什麼？
What's this acting-class guy's name?
埃利耶特
Elliot.
埃利耶特什麼？
Elliot what?
埃利耶特·布利策
Elliot Blitzer.
好  那我們打電話給他安排見面…
Okay, so we'll get him on the phone and arrange a meeting...
這樣就能趕緊走完"初次見面"的過場  好嗎？
so we can get through all this getting-to-know-you stuff, all right?
去哪兒？
Where?
我們應該  應該去哪兒見面？
Where should we meet?
過山車
Roller coaster.
Roller coasters.
那麼  你有價值50萬美元的可卡因
So, you have $500,000-worth of cola
你準備以20萬美元出貨
that you are unloading for $200,000.
你要一塊動物餅幹嗎？
You want an animal cracker?
謝謝
Thanks.
等等  留下大猩猩
Wait, save the gorillas.
謝謝
Thanks.
所以  你有…你有…
So, you got...
50萬美元的可卡因
$500,000-worth of cola...
你準備以20萬美元出貨
that you're unloading for $200,000.
"出貨"  這樣來描述交易真是過癮得很
"Unloading". That's a hell of a way to describe a bargain of a lifetime.
你從哪兒弄來的？
Where did you get it?
我從哪兒弄來的？
Where did I get it?
我在窗台上種植的  那裏陽光的確好
I grow it on my windowsill. See, the light is really good up there.
我住的比街面高很多  所以  你看…
I'm up high enough off the street, so, you know
別人看不見
you can't see it.
運作完美
It works perfectly.
好
Yeah.
說真的  它是哪兒來的？
Where, really, where does it come from?
- 它是哪兒來的？  - 對
- Where does it come from? - Yeah.
古柯葉
Coco leaves.
你有病  知道嗎？我走了
You're sick. You know what? I'm out of here.
埃利耶特  冷靜  冷靜
Elliot, chill out, chill out.
來吧  坐下  好嗎？
Come on, sit down here. All right?
既然來了  就好好玩  好嗎？
We're here, so let's enjoy the ride. All right?
我會告訴你的  好嗎？
I'll tell you, okay?
但你得保證你不說出去
But you got to promise one thing you'll keep it quiet.
要不是迪克跟我擔保你是好人
If Dick didn't ensure me you're good people,
- 我就直接說這他媽不管你的事了  - 好好好
- I'd just tell you it's none of your fucking business. - Okay, okay, okay.
一定會很好玩的
This is going to be fun.
咱們走
Let's go!
這件事的真相是：我有個朋友在局裏
The truth of the matter is this: I got a friend in the department.
哪個局？
What department?
哪個部門？你想啥呢  八號球？
What department? What do you think, eight ball?
警察局？
The police department?
給他一份獎勵！好了  大概一年半前…
Give the man a prize! All right, now, about a year and a half ago...
我這個朋友進了證據室
this friend of mine got access to the evidence room.
他偷走了這些可卡因  但他是個好警察  有一個妻子一個孩子
He snagged this coke, but he's a good cop with a wife and a kid.
所以他留了大約一年半  一直等到找到一個可以信任的人
So he had it for about a year and a half 'til he found a guy he could trust.
而他信任你？
And he trusts you?
他信任我  我們一起上過學  從小就認識
He trusts me, we were in 4-H together. We've known each other since childhood.
所以我就來這裏賣貨了  他是我的隱名合夥人
So I'm here handle sales, he's my silent partner.
他知道如果我搞砸了  我不會把他供出來
He knows, if I get fucked up, I won't drop dime on him.
好了嗎？更多的沒有了  你明白嗎？
Okay? No further, you understand?
好嗎？他有點偏執  我可什麼都沒告訴過你
All right? He's kind of paranoid, I didn't tell you nothing.
- 你什麼也沒聽到   - 沒有沒有  我什麼也沒聽見
- You didn't hear nothing. - No, no, I didn't hear nothing.
好勒  我們來嘍！
All right! Here we go!
飆上去  寶貝
Ride it out, baby!
耶！
Yeah!
我們要再來一次了  抓緊  埃利耶特
We're going in for another one! Hang on, Elliot!
哦  耶  我們爽到了  這主意真好
Oh, yeah, we got this puppy. This was a good idea.
埃利耶特臉色有點發青
Elliot looks a little green.
埃利耶特
Elliot.
我的樣子像是個金髮美女  大波翹臀…
Do I look like a beautiful blond with big tits and an ass...
像法式香草冰激凌那麼甜美嗎？
that tastes like French-vanilla ice cream?
什麼？
What?
我說  我的樣子像是個金髮美女  大波翹臀…
I said, do I look like a beautiful blond with big tits and an ass...
像法式香草冰激凌那麼甜美嗎？
that tastes like French-vanilla ice cream?
不
No.
不？好的  那你跟我扯這些廢話幹嘛？
No. Okay, then why are you telling me all this bullshit?
怎麼  你想搞我嗎？
What, do you want to fuck me?
克拉倫斯
Clarence.
他不舒服  哥們
He's sick, man.
- 讓我來處理  好嗎？  - 聽著
- Let me handle this, all right? - Look.
知道嗎？直說了吧
You know what? Just get it straight.
李不會冒風險  好嗎？
Lee is not into taking risks, okay?
他有幾個賣家  他跟他們交易好些年了  這些…
He's got a couple of guys, he's been dealing with them for years. These are...
他們很可靠  他們可以信賴  他們很安全
They're reliable, they're dependable, and they're safe.
"給我猜個謎  蝙蝠俠"
"Riddle me this, Batman".
我說  如果你們愛得這麼深  那你幹嘛來了？
I mean if you're so much in love with each other, what are you doing here?
我肯定你閒時有更好的事情可做
I'm sure you've got better things to do with your time
而不是整天在過山車上顛來倒去
than hanging around upside down on a roller coaster all day.
你們有興趣  因為有那麼多貨給了你們貼士
Your guy is interested because with that much shit this bring your tips...
他可以他媽的在好萊塢扮酷到天荒地老
he could play Joe-fucking-Hollywood until the wheels come off.
他可以賣掉它  他可以吸了它  他…
He can sell it, he can snort it, he...
他可以拿它扮演聖誕老人  在我看來
he can play Santa Claus with it as far as I concern.
我說  按他付的價錢  他可以擔得起四處亂撒
I mean, at the price he's paying he's been able to afford it just throw it around.
他會成為每個人最好的朋友  好嗎？
He's gonna be everybody's best friend, all right?
我是說  我不想讓他難做
I mean I'm not putting him down here.
那是他的錢  讓他愛幹什麼幹什麼吧
It's his money, let him do what ever the hell he wants.
但別指望我和我的朋友會吊在這裏…
But don't expect me and my friends to hang around...
永遠等著你們生出些膽量來  好嗎？
forever waiting for you guys to grow some guts, all right?
天爺啊
Jesus.
喂  你好
Yeah, hello.
嗨  李
Hi, Lee.
埃利耶特  今天週日
Elliot, it's Sunday.
你能否告訴我為何週日還要跟你通話？
Can you tell me why I'm talking to you on Sunday?
我整個星期還沒見夠你嗎？週日也要跟你通話？
Don't I see enough of you all week? I gotta talk to you on Sunday too ?
我…我跟你想讓我見的那個人在一起  李
I'm with that party that you wanted me to get together with, Lee.
你知道我說的是誰吧？
You know who I'm talking about?
我不敢相信  埃利耶特  你搞什麼鬼
I don't believe this. Elliot, why the hell are you talking to me...
跟我在電話裏談這個？
on my phone about that?
嗯  因為我跟…我跟這人在一起
Well, because I'm standing with the guy
他堅持要跟你說話
and he insists on talking to you.
什麼？你他媽是不是瘋了？
What, are you out of your fucking mind?
他…他…他說如果我不給你打電話  他就會對我…
He said...he said...he said that if I didn't get you on the phone, that he would leaves me my ....
你好  李  我是克拉倫斯  咱們終於說上話了
Hello, Lee, it's Clarence. At last, we speak.
首先  李  我要告訴你  我是你的超級粉絲
First of all, Lee, I want to tell you I'm a big fan of yours.
所以我想在洛城開拍《日瓦戈醫生》
That's why I want to open Dr. Zhivago in LA.
我需要你和你的能力來發行它
And I need you and your abilities to distribute it.
哦  克拉倫斯
Clarence
我不知道  克拉倫斯
I don't know. Clarence
《日瓦戈醫生》是一部大製作  你知道
Dr. Zhivago is a pretty big movie, you know.
你做過最大的電影  我們談的是很多部片子
The biggest movie you've dealt with. We're talking a lot of film here.
人犯傻才會對這樣的電影沒有一點謹慎
A man would be an idiot not to be a little cautious about a movie like that.
李  你並不傻
And, Lee, you're no idiot.
不不不  我不是說我不感興趣  克拉倫斯
No, no, no, no. I'm not saying I'm not interested, Clarence.
只不過當分銷商並不是我的全部生意
It's just that being a distributor is not what I'm all about.
我是電影製作人  你知道
I'm a movie producer, you know?
我在這世上是製作好電影的  不多…
I'm on this earth to make good movies, nothing more...
也不…哦  也許會少  有時候
and nothing, well, maybe less, sometimes.
別他媽的亂變道
Choose a fucking lane!
不  不是你  是個傻…不准給我中指
Not you, just an idiot...Don't give me the finger!
我找人他媽的殺了你
I'll fucking have you killed!
底線是  我不是派拉蒙  知道我的意思嗎？
So, bottom line is I'm not Paramount. You know what I'm saying?
我有幾個精選的分銷商打交道
I got a select few distributors I deal with
我買他們的小製作電影  我達成我想要的
I buy their little movies and I accomplish what I want acomplish
然後我就他媽的離開
and I get the fuck out of there.
非常商業  非常容易  而且非常低風險  克拉倫斯
Very business-like, very easy, and very little risk, Clarence.
李  我們談的是《日瓦戈醫生》  它抵得上那一堆片子  一年半…
Lee, we're talking Dr. Zhivago. It'll be packing them in. For a year and a half...
兩年…兩年裏除了我這一部 你不用買別人的電影  行嗎？
two years, I just... two years you're not gonna have to deal with anybody else's movie but mine, all right?
除了你的不用別人的  哦  幹嘛這麼匆忙？
Nobody's but yours. Well, what's the rush here?
我只是想能趕上在戛納發佈  明白嗎？
I just want to be able to announce the deal at Cannes, all right?
如果我有時間求愛  李  我會的
If I had time for a courtship, Lee, I would.
我會帶你出去  拉著你的手  親吻你的臉頰
I'd take you out, hold your hand, kiss your cheek to the door.
但我不是那個情況
But I'm not in that position.
我需要現在就知道 你我是否能一起上床
I need to know right now if you and I are in bed together or not.
如果你想要我的電影  李  你必須在恐懼與慾望中做出讓步
If you want my movie, Lee, you must come to terms with your fear and desire.
恐懼與慾望  是吧  克拉倫斯？
Fear and desire, huh, Clarence?
你不知道我的影片賺錢總共超過28億嗎  克拉倫斯？
Don't you know that my films have grossed more than $2.8 billion, Clarence?
讓我跟埃利耶特說話
Let me talk to Elliot.
- 你要跟埃利耶特說話？  - 讓我跟埃利耶特說話
- You want to talk to Elliot? - Let me talk to Elliot.
埃利耶特  他要跟你說
Elliot. He wants to talk to you.
嗨  李
Hi, Lee.
埃利耶特  你從哪兒認識這人的？
Elliot, where do you know this guy from?
他是迪克的一個朋友  記得嗎？
He's a friend of Dick's, remember?
誰是他媽的迪克？
Who the fuck is Dick?
你  你…
You, you...
你…你要我吸他的小弟弟？
You want me to suck his dick?
不不  誰是他媽的迪克？
No, no, who the fuck is Dick?
哦  誰是他媽的迪克？
Oh, who the fuck is Dick?
- 對  - 哦  迪克  他是我…
- Yeah.  - Oh, Dick. His my..
他是我朋友  他在我的表演班上
His my friend. He's in my acting class.
你告訴他我是個演員
You told him I'm an actor?
他行不行？他有才藝  還是…？
Is he any good? ls he talented, or...?
真的？
Really?
迪克怎麼認識這人的？
How does Dick know this guy?
他們…他們…
They...they...
他們一起長大的
They grew up together.
好了  星期三在酒店  三點
Okay, Wednesday at the hotel, 3:00.
整個演員陣容都他媽帶來  好嗎？
Bring the whole fucking cast, all right?
埃利耶特  別再打給我了  特別是在週日  好嗎？
Elliot, don't call me here anymore, especially not on Sunday, all right?
他說什麼？
What did he say?
- 好  等一下…  - 你有沒有告訴他我是演…
- Okay, just hold on for a secend... - Did you tell him I'm a
先閉嘴
Shut up for a second.
喂  你倆
Hey, you guys.
事情這麼辦
This is what's going to happen.
三點鐘在比弗利大使酒店  他想見所有人
Three o'clock, Beverly Ambassador, he wants to see everybody.
好嗎？
Okay?
然後他會跟你談
And, he'll talk to you.
如果跟你談過以後  他…
If after talking to you, he...
…喜歡你  想跟你打交道  他就會跟你打交道
likes you, wants to deal with you, he'll deal with you.
如果他不喜歡  他會說："操你"
If he doesn't, he'll say, "Fuck you,"
然後他會走出房間
and he'll walk out of the room.
- 你有沒有告訴他我是個演…  - 先閉一會兒嘴
- Did you tell him I was a...? - Shut up for a second.
而且他要一袋樣品
And he wants a sample bag.
完完全全沒問題
No problem on all counts.
太棒了
Great.
你有沒有告訴他我是個演員？
Did you tell him I was an actor?
是的  我告訴他了
Yes, I told him.
你告訴他我還不錯？
You told him I was good?
是的  我撒謊了
Yeah, I lied.
嗨
Hi.
- 你好嗎？  - 很好
- How are you doing? - Oh, pretty good.
- 你是迪克嗎？迪克·裏奇？  - 不是
- Are you Dick? Dick Richie? - No.
不  他現在不在
No, he's not here right now.
你住在這裏？
You live here?
是的  我住這裏
Yes, I do.
你算是室友？
You're sort of roommates?
正確
Exactly.
也許你能幫我  我在找一個朋友
Maybe you can help me, I'm looking for a friend of mine.
當然
Sure.
克拉倫斯·沃利  底特律來的
Clarence Worley from Detroit?
他跟一個相當漂亮的女孩在一起  叫做阿拉巴馬的
He's hanging with a real pretty girl named Alabama?
對  老兄  我知道他們  他們來過這裏
Yeah, man I know them. They've been by here.
- 你見過他們？   - 嗯哼
- You've seen them? - Yes.
他們住在這裏？
Are they staying here?
不  他們住在…
No, they're staying at the...
"狩獵摩托"汽車旅館  狩獵汽車旅館
Safari Motor, Motel Inn. Safari Motel.
- 狩獵汽車旅館  - 是的
- Safari Motel. - Yes.
你怎麼知道的？我是說  你去過嗎？
How do you know that? I mean, have you been over there?
沒  他們來過這裏  他們說要去那裏
No, they were here, and they said they were going to go there.
然後他們就去了
Then they went.
- 好嗎？  - 好  狩獵汽車旅館
- Yeah? - Yeah, Safari Motel.
狩獵汽車旅館
Safari Motel.
你要不要看看電視什麼的？他們也許會回這裏
You want to watch some TV or something? They might be back here.
不了  謝謝你
No, thank you.
好
Okay.
你待著  我也許會回來
You take care, I might be back.
好  老兄  好
Yeah, man. Okay, be cool.
不要跟我盛氣凌人的  我他媽殺了你  老兄
Don't be condescending to me, man. I'll fucking kill you, man.
我太為你自豪了  我扮演的角色好不好？
I'm so proud of you. Did I do my part okay?
阿拉巴馬  你真完美
Alabama, you were perfect.
就像忍者一樣？
Like a ninja?
就像忍者一樣
Like a ninja.
我去給咱倆弄點吃的
I'm going to go grab us something to eat.
我要跳進浴缸  弄濕全身  又滑又是泡沫  然後…
I'll go jump in the tub and get all wet, and slippery, and soapy. And...
跳上水床  看限制級電影  等你…
...hop onto that waterbed. And watch X-rated movies until you...
乖乖回到我的懷裏來
get your ass back into my loving arms.
趕緊回來
Hurry back now.
這下《渾身是膽》開拍嘍
We now return to Bullit already in progress.
抽煙嗎？
Cigarette?
不
No.
這一身不錯
That's a very nice outfit.
這個嗎？
This?
我在拉斯維加斯買的  內華達
I got this in Las Vegas, Nevada.
阿拉巴馬  我們的可卡因在哪兒？還有…
Alabama, where's our coke? And...
克拉倫斯在哪裏？
where's Clarence?
他什麼時候回來？
When's he coming back?
抱歉  我想你是走錯房間了
I'm sorry, I think you have the wrong room.
我的名字是薩蒂
My name is Sadie.
我們沒有可樂  但下面大堂裏有個百事售賣機
We don't have any Coke, but there's a Pepsi machine down the hall.
我不認識叫克拉倫斯的人  但也許我丈夫認識
I don't know anybody named Clarence. But perhaps my husband does.
你可以問他  因為他一會兒就回來
You can ask him because he'll be home in a minute.
他是打橄欖球的
He plays football.
他在練球呢
He's just at practice.
把手給我
Give me your hand.
好
Okay.
你讓你難以相信的逗人喜愛
You are unbelievably cute.
謝謝你  謝謝
Thank you. Thanks.
給我看看雙眼
Let me see those eyes.
多漂亮的臉蛋
What a face.
幫個忙  為我轉個身
Do me a favor. Turn around for me.
好
Okay.
不不不  從另一邊轉
No, no, go the other way.
好
Okay.
挺疼的  不是嗎？
That hurts, don't it?
站起來  甜心  你傷得沒那麼重
Get on your feet, sweetie. You ain't hurt that bad.
我們的可卡因在哪裏？克拉倫斯在哪裏？
Now, where's our coke? Where's Clarence?
他什麼時候回來？
And when's he comin' back?
好吧  好吧
Okay. Okay.
操你
Fuck you.
操我
Fuck me....
怎麼了  寶貝？
What's the matter, baby, huh?
不能呼吸？
Can't breathe?
你最好習慣
You better get used to that.
聞著像是漢堡包的氣味
Smells like hamburgers here.
告訴我  你們這裏最好最牛逼的漢堡是什麼？
Tell me, what is the biggest, baddest hamburger you guys got?
史蒂夫雙層辣起司漢堡
Steve's Double Chili Cheeseburger.
好  給我來兩個這樣的
All right, give me two of them bad boys.
兩份辣薯條  還有…
Two chili fries. And...
兩大杯健怡可樂
two large Diet Cokes.
還要別的嗎？
Anything else?
過來
Come here.
看看你自己  好好看看
Look at yourself, look! Take a good look!
你覺得你男朋友能看得下去？
You think your boyfriend would go for that shit?
要是你以為能那你就他媽太蠢了  知道嗎？
If you do you're fucking stupid. You know that?
你是很漂亮的女孩
You're a very pretty girl.
要記住你不會那麼漂亮很久的
Now remember but you ain't gonna be very pretty for very long.
我要問你一個他媽的問題
I'm gonna ask you a fucking question.
你得給我他媽的正確答案
And you give me the right fucking answer!
現在…
Now...
我的可卡因在哪裏？
where's my coke?
轉過來  轉過來
Turn around. Turn around!
回答我
Answer me!
說吧
Come on.
你心思挺多啊
You got a lot of heart, kid.
（《新聞週刊》 埃爾維斯）
對  這是個大問題
Yeah, that is a great issue.
你讀到埃爾維斯那篇了嗎？
You gotten to the story on Elvis yet?
不  還沒有
No. I hadn't.
那可能是我這輩子讀過…
That's probably the single best piece...
有關埃爾維斯·普雷斯利最棒的一篇了
I've read on Elvis Presley in my entire life.
看這裏
Look at this.
看
Look.
瞧  它試圖查明這麼多年來他的吸引力是什麼
See, it tries to pin down what the attraction is after all these years.
覆蓋了整個範圍
It covers the whole spectrum.
跟粉絲談
Talks to the fans...
跟他一起長大的人  愛他的音樂的人
people who grew up with him and people who love his music.
然後是狂熱信徒  對嗎？
Then, there's the fanatics. Right?
我不知道你怎樣  但他們讓我起雞皮疙瘩
I don't know about you, but they give me the creeps.
對對對  我明白你的意思  看這裏
Yeah, yeah, I see what you mean. Look at that...
對  我說  看看她
Yeah. I mean, look at her.
看著像是她從那顆丑樹上掉下來  一路撞上每一根枝杈
Looks like she fell off the ugly tree and hit every branch on the way down.
你第一次殺人  那是最難的
Now the first time you kill somebody, that's the hardest.
我不管你是他媽的亢奮還是開膛手傑克
I don't give a shit if you're fuckin' wired up, or Jack the Ripper.
記得德克薩斯那個人嗎？
Remember that guy in Texas?
那人在他媽的塔樓上  殺了底下好多人
The guy up in that fucking tower, killed all them people?
我拿鈔票跟你賭  他打掉的那第一個小黑點…
I bet you green money, the first little black dot he took a beat on...
那是重中之重
that was the bitch of the bunch.
第一個很困難  不開他媽的玩笑
First one is tough. No fucking fooling.
第二個  第二個也不是他媽的狂歡節
The second one. The second one ain't no fuckin' Mardi Gras...
但要比第一個好些  因為你仍然有同樣的感覺…
but it's better than the first one, 'cause you still feel the same thing, you know...
只是被稀釋了
except it's more diluted.
你知道  要更好些
You know, it's better.
我殺第一個時吐了  你相信嗎？
I threw up on the first one, you believe that?
然後是第三個
Then the third one.
第三個容易  你馬上就擺平了
The third one is easy, you level right off.
那沒問題  現在嘛…靠
That's no problem. Now.... Shit!
現在  我做事只是他媽為了看看他們不同的表現
Now, I do it just to watch their fuckin' expression change.
我他媽不敢相信
I don't fuckin' believe it.
是不是你把它放在床下的？
Did you put it under the bed?
我不敢相信  你把它放在他媽的床下
I can't believe it. You put it under the fucking bed.
我沒往他媽的床底下看
I didn't look under the fuckin' bed.
我不敢相信你把它放在他媽的床下
I can't believe you put under the fucking bed.
我不敢相信我沒有往床下看
I can't believe I didn't look under the bed.
我他媽越來越老了
I'm getting fucking old.
旅途終點  寶貝
Journey's end baby.
彩虹盡頭的雪花
Snow at the end of the rainbow.
少了一件我他媽要操心的事
One less thing I gotta fucking worry about.
就這樣了  寶貝
This is it, baby.
關鍵時刻
Moment of truth.
你心思挺多  知道嗎
You got a lot of heart, kid, you know that?
你想玩嗎？
You want to play?
這是你想要的嗎？
ls that what you want?
你想跟哥玩玩？
You want to play with Daddy?
來吧
Come on.
來啊  我給你一個機會  因為我喜歡你
Come on I'll give you one shot because I like you.
刺進來啊  寶貝  來刺你哥啊
Stick it in me, baby. Come on stick it in Daddy.
把它戳進來  來啊
Stick it in me. Go ahead.
來吧
Come on!
媽了個逼
Motherfucker!
好啊  他媽的不扮好人了
All right. No more Mr. Fucking Nice Guy.
哦  天
Oh, God!
這下你有何感想  寶貝？
What do you think of that, baby?
這下你有何感想  寶貝？你怎麼想的？
What do you think about that, baby? How would you think about that?
等等  等等
Wait! Wait!
怎麼？
What?
你他媽的笑什麼？
What the fuck are you laughing at?
你模樣真可笑
You're looking ridiculous!
過來  我他媽模樣可笑！
Come here! I look fucking ridiculous!
起來  好好笑笑  寶貝
Get up! Laugh it up, baby!
來啊  笑啊
Come on, laugh it up!
你一分鐘前還在歇斯底里  笑吧！
You were in hysterics a minute ago, so laugh!
你喜歡這樣  對嗎？
You like that, don't you?
我操
Fuck you!
靠
Shit!
操
Fuck!
靠  芭瑪  芭瑪  我們得走了  老天
Motherfucker! Bama, Bama we gotta go! Jesus Christ!
來  親愛的  我們他媽得離開這裏
Come on, darling. We gotta get the fuck out of here!
來
Come on.
條子他媽的隨時會來
The cops are gonna be here any fucking second!
操
Fuck!
操  快快
Fuck, come on!
操
Fuck!
對不起  對不起  對不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
他媽的讓路
Get the fuck out of the way!
哦  操
Oh, fuck!
操
Fuck!
- 怎麼了？  - 我他媽的不敢相信
- What? - I don't fucking believe this!
老天  我就知道  我他媽的就知道
Goddamn it! I knew it! I fucking knew it!
開車開成這樣我腦袋該去檢查
I should have my goddamn head examined for driving like this.
你看  卡拉…
Look Carla....
坎蒂…
Kandi....
坎蒂  你得幫我
Kandi, you've got to help me.
我能做什麼？
What can I do?
拿著這個  拿好
Take this. Hold this.
什麼？你嗨了吧？不要
What are you? High? No.
他媽的把這東西放你包裏
Fucking put this in your purse.
我不要把那東西放我包裏
I'm not putting that shit in my purse.
他不會搜查你的  你又沒幹什麼
He's not gonna search you. You didn't do anything.
那就放在你胸罩裏
Now just put it in your bra!
我沒穿啊
I'm not wearing one.
求你了  他快來了  放在你他媽的褲子裏
Please, he's almost here! Just fucking put it in your pants!
不
No.
是你要開快的
You're the one who wanted to drive fast.
看我口型  不！
Read my lips. No.
- 我為你做了那麼多  你他媽的妓女！  - 混蛋
- After all I did for you, you fuck whore!  -Asshole.
你他媽以為你是誰？
Who the fuck do you think you...?
聽好  傻屌  你運氣不好我們抓到你超速
Look, dickhead. It's your bad luck that we caught you speeding...
而且你運氣不好  有一袋沒分包的可卡因在你…
and it's your bad luck that you had a bag of uncut cocaine in your...
- 可不是一小瓶  - …他媽的包裏
- Not a little vial. - ...motherfucking baggy.
喂  你被抓了
Hey, you got caught.
沒抓到你你他媽的玩得挺開心  現在我們逮到你了
It's all fun fucking games until you get caught. Now we got you.
好嗎  埃利耶特先生  他媽的演員  你剛創造了高光時刻
Okay, Mr. Elliot, fucking actor, you just made the big time.
- 你不再是臨時演員…  - 或是跑龍套的
- You're no longer an extra... - Or a bit player.
- 或是配角  - 你他媽的成明星了
- or a supporting actor. - You're a fucking star.
你他媽的成明星了
You're a fucking star.
你要出演你的個人秀節目…
And you're gonna be playing your one-man show...
以後兩年裏他媽的每晚上演
nightly for the next two fucking years!
為一幫不會走開的觀眾
For a captive audience.
聽好了  你過幾年會出來  遇到個老女人
Listen to this. You'll get out in a few years and meet some old lady.
你會結婚  然後你會非常瞭解你老婆的各種需求…
You'll get married and you'll be so understanding to your wife's needs...
因為你知道當一個女人是什麼樣的感受
because you'll know what it feels like to be a woman.
你只會想操她的屁股  因為她的屄對你來說不夠緊了
You'll only want to fuck her ass 'cause her pussy just won't be tight enough for you anymore.
說得好  警探
Good point, Detective.
對嗎？他媽的相公
Right? Fucking faggot!
克林柯  就是它  我們逮到了  全是我們的
Krinkle, this is it, we got it, man, and it's all ours.
我是說  說起碰巧撞上…
I mean, you talk about falling into something....
你們他媽的閉嘴  我能聽懂
Would you idiot shut up! I can't understand shit.
好了  出什麼事了？怎麼了？你們在說什麼？
Now, what happened? What's gonna on? What are you talking about?
好了  是這樣
Okay, all right.
巡邏車截停了一輛超速車  瞭解？
Patrol car pulls a guy over for speeding, right?
嫌犯滿身可卡因…
Suspect is covered with coke...
所以他們把嫌犯帶給我和尼科爾森  我們審了他
so they bring suspect to me and Nicholson. We got a work on him.
"尼科爾森和我"
Nicholson and l.
尼科爾森  有他媽的什麼區別？
Nicholson, what's the fucking difference?
所以我們審了這人  瞭解？
So we go to work on that guy, all right?
我們知道其中必有古怪
We know something is rotten in Denmark
因為這人太他媽笨了  而他還有一大袋可卡因  還是沒分包的
'cause this guy is fucking stupid, and he's got a big bag of coke, and it's uncut.
你都不會相信他說的
And you aren't gonna fucking believe what he's got to say.
看起來某個警局的一名警察  我們不知道是哪個
Seems a cop from some department, we don't know which one...
他從財物室偷了50萬美元的可卡因
he stole $500,000 worth of coke from the property cage....
他把這玩意兒藏了一年半  明白嗎？
He sat on the shit for a year and a half, okay?
- 現在  這警察派了一個怪人…  - 嫌犯的原話
- Now, the cop's got this weirdo... - Suspect's words.
…來為他打點  明白嗎？
to front for him all right?
所以我們的嫌疑人埃利耶特·布利策
So our guy, Elliot Blitzer
他在他們和他的老闆之間牽頭…
he is making a deal between them and his boss...
他媽的當紅電影製作人  名叫李·多諾維茨
big-time fucking movie producer named Lee Donowitz.
他製作了那部《裝在屍袋中回家》
He did the movie Coming Home in a Body Bag.
一部越戰片？
A Vietnam movie?
- 對  - 他媽的好電影
- Yeah. - Good fucking movie.
他媽的A級  他媽的真是棒電影
Fucking A. Great fucking movie.
那麼  你相信他嗎？
So, do you believe him?
我相信他相信他
I believe he believes him.
這人的慌亂緊張得不可能說謊  我跟你說
This guy is too fucking rattled to be lying. I'm telling you...
他反覆念叨他爹媽  他穿老式女褲的奶奶
He'd roll over on his mom, dad, his two-pantied granny...
還有他媽的暹羅國王  好像他跟他有什麼瓜葛一樣
and the fucking King of Siam if he had anything on him.
我說這人是個娘們兒  他真的是
I mean this guy was a sissy. I mean he really was.
這兔崽子什麼都願意幹  只要不坐牢
This rabbit will do anything not to do any time.
你知道他願意幹嘛嗎？
You know what he'll do?
他願意戴竊聽器
He'll wear a wire.
他願意戴竊聽器？
He'll wear a wire?
他願意戴竊聽器  我們跟他講了
He'll wear a wire, we talked to him.
貪腐警察  我們得讓內務部來
Dirty cops, well, we got to get Internal Affairs on this.
我才不管你讓誰介入  警監
I don't give a shit who you bring in, Captain.
你可以讓#$%^（沒聽清）介入…
You can bring in the state enlisted LA...
他媽的史蒂芬·麥奎因的鬼魂  十個他媽的羅馬角鬥士
the ghost of Steve fucking McQueen, ten fucking Roman gladiators.
我管他個鳥  只要托德和我能在這雜種身上撈到好處
I don't give a shit as long as me and Todd get credit for the bust.
聽著  是我們發現的  我們只想要他媽的領花[升職]
Listen, we found him. We just want the fucking collar.
就這樣  故事講完
That's it. End of story.
就這麼辦
You got it.
我跟你說過我有多討厭機場嗎？
Did I ever tell you how much I hate airports?
你看  我在迪爾伯恩時曾住過一個機場旁邊
See, I used to live by one back in Dearborn, you know.
你一無所成住在機場旁邊真的很喪
Really frustrating living next to an airport when you don't got shit.
而我整天…
And all day long I'm...
看著聽著別人做的 正是我想做而不能做的事情
seeing and hearing people doing exactly what I want to be doing, but couldn't.
什麼事？
What?
開始新生活  住在底特律
Starting new lives, leaving Detroit
度假  出差…
vacations, business trips...
好玩  好玩  好玩
fun, fun, fun.
好了
All right.
你和我  咱們能跳上那邊隨便一架飛機…
You and me, we can jump on any one of those planes out there...
想去哪裏就去哪裏  給我一種全新的視野
and go anywhere we want. Gives me a whole new outlook.
能實現就愛死了
Love how it works out.
對  你沒開玩笑  我們重新開始生活
Yeah, you're not kidding. We got lives to start over.
我們應該去一個我們能白手起家的地方
We should go somewhere where we can start from scratch.
我這輩子一直待在美國
I've been in America all my life.
我想看看別的國家的電視是什麼樣
I'd like to see what TV in other countries looks like.
你覺得咱們應該去哪兒  小斑鳩
Where do you think we should go, my little turtle dove?
坎昆
Cancun.
坎昆  為什麼去坎昆？
Cancun, why Cancun?
聽起來很不錯的樣子  像是一部電影名字
It's got a nice ring to it. It sounds like a movie.
《克拉倫斯和阿拉巴馬去坎昆》  你覺得如何？
Clarence and Alabama Go to Cancun, don't you think?
在我的電影裏  親愛的  你是頭牌明星
In my movie, darling, you get top billing.
你什麼也不要擔心  好嗎？
Don't you worry about nothing, all right?
我們一切都會順利的
It's all going to work out for us.
我們應得的
We deserve it.
弗洛伊德  你確定你要那樣去比弗利大使酒店？
Floyd, you sure that's how you get to the Beverly Ambassador?
是的  哥們  我肯定
Yeah, man, I'm positive.
我告訴你  要是我們失手了  就是你的錯
Let me tell you, if we get lost that's your ass.
還有  弗洛伊德  你怎麼不放過我的啤酒  去找個他媽的工作？
And Floyd, why don't you get out of my beer and get a fucking job?
- 好好  - 克拉倫斯
- Yeah, okay.  - Clarence
- 我們能走了嗎？   - 我們出門了
- Can we go? - We're out the door.
我們必須在大堂見埃利耶特  我不想遲到  快點
We must meet Elliot in the lobby. I don't wanna be late, come on.
你沒事吧？
You all right?
喂
Yes.
- 我出去了  弗洛伊德  - 你在嗎？不  他不在
- I'm out, Floyd.  - Are you here? No, he's not here.
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait!
- 快點  迪克  - 等等
- Come on, Dick!  - Wait.
你好？
Hello?
嗨  "警監"  我剛要出門…
Hey. Hi, Captain, I was just walkin' out...
什麼？
What?
認真的？
Serious?
她說的？
She said that?
她說什麼？快來吧
What did she say? Come on, okay?
喂  "警監"  謝謝你  謝謝你
Yo, Captain, thank you, thank you.
嗨  "警監"
Hi, Captain
我明天再跟你談
I'm going to talk to you tomorrow.
好的
All right.
快  我們得走了
Come on, we got to go.
快來
Come on.
我拿到那個角色了
I got the part.
- 帥啊  老兄  - 我拿到那個角色了
That's perfect, man.  - I got the part.
太棒了  好極了
That's great. That's wonderful.
都沒想過會有回電
Didn't even want a callback.
太酷了  加油啊
That's so cool, way to go!
我接到了"七點電話"
I got a 7:00 call.
太好了  好了  來吧  咱們走
That's great. All right, come on, let's go.
我要聽到全部過程  好嗎？來吧
I want to hear all about it, okay? Come on.
喂  克拉倫斯
Hey, Clarence!
什麼？
What?
沒什麼  算了
Nothing. Forget it.
好了  走吧
All right, come on.
喂  買些…買些啤酒
Hey, get some... get some beer.
再買些…
and some...
再買些清潔用品
and some cleaning products.
我丟了他媽一筆錢在這裏
I'm losing a fucking fortune over here.
你跟我說話嗎  他媽的意大利佬？
You talkin' to me, you fucking wop, you?
穿上外衣  穿上外衣
Put your jacket on. Put your jacket on.
- 準備好了？  - 是
- Ready? - Yeah.
穿上外衣
Put your jacket on.
一次一隻袖子
One sleeve at a time.
重大比賽了  埃利耶特
It's a big game, now, Elliot.
沒事的  振作點  你還好嗎?
It's okay, come on. You all right?
不好
No.
埃利耶特  看著我
Elliot, look at me.
看著我  你舒服嗎？
Look at me. You comfortable?
我舒服嗎？我有一個…
Am I comfortable? I've got a...
就像是…你知道的…磚頭在陰囊上
like a, you know, brick in my scrotum.
那是最佳的地方  知道嗎？
That's the best place for it, okay?
如果他們拍你搜身  不會搜查你的蛋蛋
It they  pat-down you, they're not gonna search your balls.
好吧  你覺得他們會不會看見這東西？
Okay, you think they might see this perhaps?
- 不會  沒事的  你站起來就沒事  - 好吧
- No. It's okay. When you stand up, it'll be okay.  - Okay.
- 埃利耶特  - 在
- Elliot.  - Yeah?
說點什麼
Say something.
好  嗨  你好嗎？
Okay. Hi. How are you?
我叫埃利耶特  我正跟美國童子軍在一起
My name is Elliot, and I'm with the Cub Scouts of America.
我們在賣沒拆包的可卡因  為了能參加童子軍大會
We're, we're selling uncut cocaine to get to the jamboree.
- 平常講話就好  埃利耶特  - 抱歉
- Just talk regular, Elliot. - I'm sorry.
埃利耶特  別他媽亂來
Elliot, stop fucking around.
我不敢相信我這樣子
I can't believe I'm doing this.
你弄好了？
You get that shit?
記住  埃利耶特  整個期間我們就在下面大廳監視你們
Remember, Elliot, we'll be right down the hall monitoring you the whole time.
好  但如果有人做出什麼 你們聽不見的事怎麼辦
Yeah, but what happens if somebody does something you can't hear...
比如掏出一把槍 對著我他媽的眼睛？
like puts out a gun and put it to my fucking eye?
埃利耶特  這種事我們做過上千次…
Elliot, we've done this a thousand times.
我們知道自己在做什麼  明白嗎？
We know what we're doing. Okay?
我們是最好的  做…聽著  不要亂搞
We're the best at....Now, listen. No fucking around.
發生任何事  我們會像他媽的黑幫一樣衝進去  明白嗎？
Anything happens, we'll be in there like fucking gangbusters, okay?
現在你得記住一件事
Now you get to remember something.
你不想進監獄  對吧？
You don't want to go to jail, right?
你想進監獄嗎？
You want to go to jail?
不  我不想進監獄
No. I don't want to go to jail.
所以我們得怎麼做？
So, what do we got to do?
我們得把你老闆弄進監獄  明白？
We got to put your boss in jail, okay?
你要這麼做  還要在法庭上表演  消除任何合理懷疑
You do that, and you got to show in court, beyond any reasonable doubt...
這個人  一個在好萊塢社群極受尊重的人
that this man, a very respectable man in the Hollywood community...
同時在販毒
is also dealing cocaine.
我們得在法庭上證明  而你必須去做
We gotta prove it in court, and you gotta do it.
這就是我們要做的事情  明白？
That's what we're doing here, okay?
你會沒事的  你不會受傷的  明白嗎？
You're going to be okay, you're not gonna get hurt. Okay?
所以你要做的…
So what you got to do...
是一定要讓他承認
is you gotta get him to admit...
錄在帶子上  明白？
on tape, all right?
承認他要買這些可卡因  好嗎  冠軍？
That he's buying this coke. Okay, champ?
- 控制好你自己  - 好
- Get a hold of yourself. - Okay.
我去弄點咖啡
I'm going to get some coffee.
芭瑪  你真是打籃球弄的？
Bama, you really got that playing basketball?
對  我挨了一肘  正中眼睛  這還沒完…
Yes, I got an elbow right in the eye. Then like that's not enough...
我被球砸了一下  當時沒注意看
I got hurled the ball when I'm not looking.
正打在臉上
Right in my face.
你應該小心些
You should be careful.
是應該
I should.
克拉倫斯  你他媽把那東西帶來幹嘛？
Clarence, what the fuck did you bring that for?
以防萬一
In case.
萬一什麼？
In case of what?
我不知道  你想讓我說什麼？
I don't know, what do you want me to say?
聽著  克拉倫斯  李·多諾維茨不是皮條客
Look, Clarence, Lee Donowitz is not a pimp.
我知道  裏奇  但上周我被教會了一件事
I know that, Richie, but one thing this last week has taught me...
有槍而不需要它  要好過需要槍而沒有它
it's better to have a gun and not need it than to need a gun and not have it.
他在那兒
There he is.
埃利耶特  你的動機是遠離牢房
Elliot, your motivation is to stay out of jail.
放鬆放鬆放鬆
Easy, easy, easy.
我估計時間差不多了
I guess it's about that time.
對
Yeah.
咱們走
Here we go.
你是演員  演戲啊  媽個逼的
You're an actor. Act, motherfucker.
埃利耶特
Elliot.
怎麼？
Yeah?
跪下來
Get on your knees.
哦不
Oh, no.
什麼？
What?
- 我說他媽的跪下  - 搞他媽什麼？
- I said get the fuck on your knees! - What the fuck?
他媽的閉嘴  你們倆！我他媽知道自己在幹嘛
Shut the fuck up, both of you! I know what the fuck I'm doing.
你以為我他媽的很蠢  是不是？是不是？
You think I'm pretty fucking stupid, don't you? Don't you?
- 不  - 不？你他媽別撒謊  媽個逼的
- No.  - No? Don't you fucking lie to me, you motherfucker!
他在詐你  埃利耶特  他在詐你  你看不出來嗎？
He's bluffing you, Elliot. He's bluffing you. Can't you see that?
快點  我要聽見你說
Come on, I want to hear you say...
我要聽見你說：克拉倫斯  你毫無疑問是…
I want to hear you say "Clarence, you are, without a doubt..."
- 克拉倫斯  怎麼了？  - 閉嘴
- Clarence, what's wrong? - Shut up!
說啊  該死的  我要聽見你說出來
Say it, god damn it! I want to hear you say it!
"克拉倫斯  你毫無疑問是我在這地球上見過最愚蠢的二貨"
"Clarence, you are, without a doubt, the dumbest motherfucker I've ever seen on this planet".
- 說啊  - 媽蛋
- Say it! - Dumb fucker.
- 顯然  我沒有…  - 克拉倫斯  他什麼也沒幹  - 閉嘴好嗎？
- Apparently, I'm not as dumb... - Clarence, he didn't do nothing!  - Shut up, all right?
顯然  我沒有你他媽以為的那麼蠢  對吧？
Apparently, I'm not as dumb as you fucking think I am, am I?
快說  上面到底有他媽什麼在等我們？
Come on, what the fuck is waiting for us up there?
他媽的什麼在等我們？
What the fuck's waiting for us?
他要開槍了
He's going to shoot him.
- 告訴我  要不我給你臉上穿兩個窟窿  此時此刻  - 他沒幹什麼
- Tell me, or I'll pump two in your face right here and now.  - He didn't do it.
他不會開槍的
He's not going to shoot him.
媽了個逼
Motherfuck!
他會開槍
He's going to shoot him.
就像尼克·庫裏以前說的
Like Nick Curry used to say
"要是我錯了  我對天發誓  我他媽道歉"  對吧？
"If I'm wrong I swear to god I'll fucking apologize" all right?
事情有差錯  我能感覺到
Something's amiss, I can feel it.
如果出了什麼事  我對天發誓  你是第一個挨槍的
If anything strange goes down, I swear to god, you're gonna be the first one shot.
克拉倫斯  他什麼也沒幹  你他媽幹嘛
Clarence, he didn't do anything, what the fuck are you...
閉嘴！好了  我要崩了這他媽逼的
Shut up! All right, I'll blow this motherfucker away.
我操
Fuck you!
我希望有關的人能來救我  因為我再也不喜歡這樣了
I wish somebody with this come and get me because I don't like this anymore!
控制住自己  你他媽的娘炮
Get a hold of yourself, you fucking sissy!
我真心希望有關的人能來帶我出去  帶我出去
I really wish somebody with this just come and take me away! Just take me away!
堅持住  埃利耶特  該死的
Hang in there, Elliot, goddamn it!
我受不了了  對不起  但我撐不住了
I can't take this, I'm sorry, but I just can't!
我希望有人來救我  什麼事都不會有
I wish somebody would just come to my rescue and everything will be all right.
埃利耶特
Elliot.
- 埃利耶特  - 什麼？
- Elliot.   - What?
抱歉  好嗎？
I'm sorry, all right?
抱歉  抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
還是朋友？
Friends?
抱歉  老兄
I'm sorry, man
這人他媽的什麼毛病？
What the fuck is with this guy?
別再亂整了
Quit playing around.
我不是亂整  我只是得確認
I wasn't playing around, I just had to be sure.
就是這樣  就這樣  我現在確定了  好嗎
That's all, that's all. I'm sure now, okay?
抱歉  老兄  我不是有意嚇唬你
I'm sorry, man. I didn't mean to scare you.
哎喲  我喜歡這個克拉倫斯小子  這傢伙他媽的夠瘋
Oh, man, I like this Clarence kid, this fucking guy is crazy.
在
Yeah.
哎喲
Oh, man.
你是迪克·裏奇嗎？
Are you Dick Richie?
不是
No.
你認識一個克拉倫斯·沃利嗎？
Do you know a Clarence Worley?
是的
Yes.
- 你知道我們在哪兒能找到他嗎？  - 對  我知道
- Do you know where we can find him?  - Yes, I do.
那是哪兒呢？
Well, where?
在比弗利大使酒店
At the Beverly Ambassador.
那地方在哪裏？
Where's that?
哦
Well....
你走…
You go....
不…對  沿著…沿著比奇伍德
No. Yeah, go down...Go down Beachwood
你們想不想抽一壺？
You guys want to smoke a bowl, or....
哦  沿著比奇伍德
Oh. Go down Beachwood...
開上一段  然後你得右轉  明白？
and drive awhile, and then you gotta turn right, okay?
然後你繼續  繼續開  繼續開
And then you go, and you keep driving and you keep driving.
你好  埃利耶特
Hello, Elliot.
蒙蒂
Monty.
這是你的朋友？
Are these your friends?
對  對  你可以這麼說
Yeah, yeah, you could say that.
各位  這是蒙蒂
Everybody, this is Monty.
嗨  進來吧  李剛殺青  他很快出來
Hi. Come on in. Lee's in the can, he'll be out in a quick.
我的個神  看看  你相信嗎？
Holy shit, look at this. Do you believe this?
那是直升機
It's a helicopter.
抱歉  不是針對你
Sorry, it's nothing personal.
克拉倫斯
Clarence.
沒必要搜查我  勇士
There'll be no need to search me, daredevil.
你要找的在這裏
All you'll find is this right here.
你出於什麼理由帶那東西來？
Now what compelled you to bring that along?
同樣的理由促成你們…
The same thing that compelled you guys to...
帶著重型火炮來談生意
bring heavy artillery to a business meeting.
我來拿
I'll take that.
哦  必須的
Well, you're going to have to.
大家都在這兒了
Everybody's here.
埃利耶特  誰是誰？
Elliot. Who's who?
那是迪克  在那頭
That's Dick on the end there.
哦  那是迪克
Oh, that's Dick.
迪克  埃利耶特告訴我你很有天分
Dick, Elliot tells me you're quite gifted.
還有  對  阿拉巴馬在中間
And, yeah, Alabama in the middle.
你好
Hello.
克拉倫斯在這邊
Clarence on the end.
- 李  這人帶著…  - 鮑裏斯
- Lee, this guy is.... - Boris
拜託  我正在會客  好嗎？
please. I'm meeting people right now, okay?
多諾維茨先生？
Mr. Donowitz?
好了  克拉倫斯  別臊我了  叫我"李"好了
Come on. Clarence, don't insult me, just call me "Lee".
- 李  - 鮑裏斯  閉你媽嘴
- Lee. - Boris, shut the fuck up!
來吧  大家  別害羞  進來進來
Come on, everybody, don't be shy. Come on in. Come in.
好的  叫"李"？
Okay, Lee?
- 就叫"李"  - 李
- Lee. - Lee.
對了  李
That's right, Lee.
我得告訴你  我真的是個大粉絲
I just gotta tell you, I really am a big fan.
《裝在屍袋中回家》始終是我最喜歡的電影
Coming Home In a Body Bag is my favorite movie of all time.
我是說  《現代啟示錄》之後  我覺得它就是最佳越戰片
I mean, after Apocalypse Now, I think it's the best Vietnam movie ever made.
哇  非常感謝  克拉倫斯
Wow. Thank you very much, Clarence.
- 李  - 什麼？
- Lee. - What?
這人帶著傢伙
This guy is packing.
真的？
Really.
哦  我是說  這件事真的讓我很受驚
Well, I mean, I've been pretty scared about this whole thing.
但我相當確信你是來做生意的  所以你看
But, I'm fairly confident you're here to do business, so look.
我不想當自作聰明的人
I don't want to be a wise guy and nothing.
如果你喜歡  我就把槍拿出來放在桌上
If you want, I'll take my gun and I will lay it on the table.
全看你
It's up to you.
不  我覺得沒必要
No, I don't think that's necessary.
鮑裏斯  態度好點  給大家弄點咖啡  好嗎？
Boris, be nice. Make everybody some coffee. Okay?
- 很高興見到你  - 我也很高興
- It's a pleasure to meet you. - Nice to meet you, too.
親  坐吧  放鬆  放鬆
Honey, sit down. Relax, relax.
埃利耶特  你臉色跟屎一樣
Elliot, you look like shit.
哦  對不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
我說  真是太噁心了
I mean, it's completely disgusting.
嗯  要是能快速給我簽個名  就太好了
If I could get a quick signature, it would be great.
邦妮高興就好
Whatever Bonnie wants.
喜歡那個樣片  克拉？
Like my dailies, there, Clar?
這就是樣片嗎？
Is that what these are, dailie?
- 你喜歡嗎？  - 對  太棒了
- You like them? - Yeah, they're great.
他媽的最好如此  花了我好多錢
They better fucking be, they cost me enough.
那天花了我多少？
What did that day cost me?
35萬7千
$357,000.
埃利耶特  我對天發誓  有人在從我這裏偷錢
Elliot, I swear to God, somebody is stealing from me.
這一部叫什麼？
What's this one called, anyway?
它是續集  《屍袋》的
It's a sequel to Body Bag.
真的？
Really?
我們還沒取好名字  不過…喬喜歡哪個？
We don't have a title yet, but...what does Joe like?
《屍袋二》
Body Bags Two.
哦  很有想像力
Oh. That's imaginative.
我的陰莖品味都比這高
I've got more taste in my penis.
這傢伙真他媽好玩
This guy is really fucking funny.
你看  李  多數獲得很多奧斯卡獎的影片我都受不了
You know, Lee, most of these movies that win a lot of Oscars, I can't stand them.
它們都是些安全  老態  擺設用的狗屎  你知道嗎？
They're safe, geriatric, coffee-table dog shit, you know?
咱倆意見一致
We park our cars in the same garage.
沒事
It's all right.
那些混球們把讀不成的書改編成看不成的電影
All those assholes make unwatchable movies from unreadable books.
《瘋狂的麥克斯》  是部好電影
Mad Max, that's a movie.
《黃金三鏢客》  是部好電影
The Good The Bad And The Ugly, that's a movie.
《赤膽威龍》  是部好電影
Rio Bravo, that's a movie.
還有《裝在屍袋中回家》  那是他媽的好電影
And Coming Home in a Body Bag, that was a fucking movie.
那是得過奧斯卡的電影中唯一有種的
It was the only movie up that time won Oscars with balls...
我是說繼《獵鹿人》之後
I mean, since Deerhunter.
我真不敢相信你
I don't believe you.
怎麼  你想倒點咖啡來配糖嗎？
What, do you like a little coffee with your sugar, or what?
李  這茶匙不立起來我是不會滿意的
Lee, I'm not satisfied until the spoon stands straight up.
給我一杯咖啡  好嗎
Give me a coffee, will you?
李  我叔叔羅傑和傑瑞  倆人都從越南回來的
Lee, my uncle Roger and my uncle Jerry, both from Vietnam...
看過《裝在屍袋中回家》
saw Coming Home in a Body Bag.
他們對我說  克拉倫斯  那是他們見過最精確的越戰片
They said to me, Clarence, that's the most accurate Vietnam film they'd ever seen.
我告訴你  克拉倫斯  那場狗屎戰爭中的老兵這樣說我的項目
I'll tell you something, Clarence. When veterans in that bullshit war say that about my project...
讓這東西完全值了
it makes the whole thing worthwhile.
這杯敬你
Here's to you.
我的朋友  喔  叫你"我的朋友"  而我剛認識你
My friend, oops, call you my friend, I just met you.
知道為什麼嗎？
You know why?
我想是因為我們有共同的興趣
I think because we got the same interests.
你知道我現在想做什麼嗎？
And you know what I'd like to do right now?
我想看看《日瓦戈醫生》
I'd like to see Dr. Zhivago.
它在哪裏？
Where is it?
這房子裏他媽的有沒有一個醫生  還是怎麼的？
Is there a fucking doctor in the house, or what?
先等一下
Hang on a second.
李  你看見它時  你會…
Lee, when you see this, you are going to shit...
- 最好如此  - 中了
- I better.  - Bingo
- 那人叫什麼名字？  - 多諾維茨
- What's the guy's name? - Donowitz.
李  這是完全沒分包的  如果你這麼渴望…
Lee, that's all practically uncut. If you so desire...
你可以分開摻成更多
you can cut that a lot more.
別擔心  我會渴望的
Don't worry, I'll desire.
鮑裏斯  再給我一杯咖啡  好嗎？
Boris, get me another cup of coffee, will you?
我也要  鮑裏斯
Me, too, Boris.
我不得不給你點贊  克拉倫斯  這不是一般貨色
I have to hand it to you, Clarence, this is not nose garbage.
這是優質品
This is quality stuff.
完美的貨物  唯一的麻煩是…
Perfect merchandise. The only trouble is...
不論何時有人跟我提出一項好得太過分的交易
whenever I'm offered a deal that's too good to be true...
都是出於謊話而已
it's because it's a lie.
老天
Jesus
你不妨說服我你是誠實可靠的
Why don't you convince me you're on the level.
說服他
Convince him.
要是他不咬鉤  我們除了持有罪沒別的可抓
If he don't bite, we aien't got shoot except possession.
鮑裏斯  我們這有好多東西  給大家弄點
Boris, we got lots of sandwich shit back there, make something for someone.
我們有煙熏牛肉  黑麥…誰要點什麼？
We got pastrami, nice rye....anybody want anything?
你們有阿司匹林嗎？
You, got any aspirin?
有  當然  給他
Yeah, sure. Get him that.
好吧  李  是這樣的
Well, Lee, it's like this.
瞧  你撿到這個畢生難逢的便宜  是因為我他媽不知道該怎麼做
See, you're getting this bargain of life time because I don't know what the fuck I'm doing.
你習慣跟專業人士交易  而我不是專業的  我是外行
You're used to dealing with professionals and I'm not professional. I'm a rank amateur.
他媽的搞什麼？他媽的搞什麼  喬？
What the fuck is going on? What's the fuck is going on, Joe?
我可以接受  比如一次賣一點點
I can take that, like sell it a little bit at a time...
比如多賺上好多錢
like make a hell of a lot more money.
怎麼回事  喬？
What's going on, Joe?
怎麼回事？埃利耶特離太遠了
What's going on? Elliot's too far away.
（#$%^&*）
我不是毒販  我不是說你是毒販  你是他媽的電影製作人
Now, I'm not a drug deal, I'm not saying that you're a drug dealer,
但你在錢啊等等這些玩意上有門路
And you got access to all kinds of money and shit like that.
靠
Shit.
- 哦  喬  你他媽急死我了  - 等等等等
- Oh, Joe you are fucking killing me. - Wait, wait.
- 喬  - 等等  噓
- Joe  - There, wait, hush.
看  我不能靠它賺到百萬  但你能  對吧？
Now, I can't get a million for it, but you can, all right?
所以我20萬賣給你  你去用它賺一百萬
So I'll sell it to you for $200,000. You go make a million with it.
靠  反正對我來說全是白撿的錢  知道嗎？
Shit, it's all found money to me anyway, you know?
有了
There he is.
我和我妻子  我們是賺最低工資的小孩  知道嗎？
Me and my wife, we're minimum-wage kids, you know?
20萬美元  對於我們就是整個世界
$200,000. It means the world to us.
你真酷
埃利耶特告訴我你是為一個貪腐警察打前站的
Elliot tells me that you're fronting for a dirty cop.
埃利耶特什麼都不該跟你說的
Elliot wasn't supposed to tell you anything.
他不是貪腐警察  他是個好警察
Now, he's not a dirty cop, he's a good cop.
他只是…你知道的  他看到自己的機會然後抓住了  就這樣
He just...you know, he saw his chance and he took it, that's all.
他為什麼信任你？
Why does he trust you?
我們一起長大的  就這原因
Well, we grew up together, that's why.
克拉倫斯
Clarence.
如果你屁都不懂  那他為什麼認為你能賣掉它？
If you don't know shit, then why does he think that you can sell it?
我跟他胡吹的
I bullshitted him.
你真是瘋子
You're nuts!
他挺狂的  這小子克拉倫斯  我喜歡他
He's a wild man, this kid, Clarence. I like him.
- 你真狂  我喜歡  - 嘿  李
- You're wild, I love it. - Hey, Lee.
我愛這傢伙  他跟他胡吹  你相信這小子嗎？我愛他
I love this guy, he bullshitted him, you believe this kid? I love him.
埃利耶特  我愛這小子
Elliot, I love this kid.
蒙蒂  拿錢
Monty, get the money.
就是它了  夥計們  咱們去抓這幫狗娘養的
That's it, fellas, let's get these son of bitches.
那個  等等  我完全忘了  請原諒
Now wait, wait. I completely forgot, excuse me.
- 你在這裏是什麼角色？ - 我是他妻子
- What's your part in this again? - I'm his wife.
哦  你就是那個妻子  好
Oh, you're the wife, right.
克拉倫斯  克拉倫斯
Clarence, Clarence.
你做了什麼  打了她還是怎麼？
What did you do, beat her or something?
不不  她打籃球弄的
No, she got that playing basketball.
- 你怎麼回事？ - 抱歉
- What's the matter with you? - I'm sorry.
你為什麼來？
Why are you here?
我…我是個演員
I'm an actor.
迪克  如果你只是個他媽的演員  你永遠也進不了這房間
Dick, if you were just a fucking actor, you never would have got in the room.
我…我是埃利耶特的朋友
I'm friends with Elliot.
他是你朋友？你有麻煩了
He's your friend? You got problems.
好了  沒關係  埃利耶特知道我
All right. It's all right. Elliot knows me.
埃利耶特  給
Elliot, here.
打給喬  告訴那個吸屌的  製片經理跟我報告說…
Call Joe and tell that cock sucker the production manager reports to me...
他從每1美元裏抽30美分…
he's taking 30 cents of every dollar...
裝進自己的腰包
and putting it in his own pocket.
你不想數數你的錢嗎？
Don't you want to count your money?
不  沒事的  她能數  我要去洗手間
No, that's all right, she can count it. I'm going to the bathroom.
給她
Give it to her.
我得給你點贊  克拉倫斯
I gotta hand it to you, Clarence.
- 我剛才挺酷？  - 老兄  你比酷還酷
- I was cool? - Man, you were cooler than cool.
哦  我的天  我忘了他媽的防彈背心了
Oh, my God, I forgot my fucking vest.
蠢
Stupid.
- 科迪  數到三  - 好
- Cody, on three.  - Yeah.
一 二 三
One. Two. Three!
別動  別動！
Freeze, freez!
放下槍
Put your guns down!
趴到地板上
Get down on the floor!
扔掉槍
Drop your gun!
扔下槍往後退
Drop your guns and back away!
你們倆把他媽的槍扔地板上  馬上！
Both of you put the fucking guns on the floor now!
草泥馬
Fuck you!
你們這些豬玀  槍扔地板上  往後退
All you pigs! Put your guns on the floor and back away!
蒙蒂蒙蒂  你怎麼了  他媽的瘋了？照他們說的做
Monty! What are you, fucking nuts? Just do what they say!
夥計  這是你他媽最後的機會
Man this is your last fucking chance!
草泥馬  這是你們最後的機會
Fuck you, this is your last chance!
啥  鮑裏斯？
What, Boris?
我們可以殺光你們全部  你們也知道
We could kill all of you and you fucking know it.
趴在他媽的地板上
Get down on the fucking floor!
鮑裏斯  你他媽閉嘴
Boris, shut the fuck up!
我們全都得死在這裏  這是警察
We're all going to die here, these are cops.
哦  他們是警察  誰當回事？
So, they're cops. Who gives a shit!
喂  李  我有一件事從沒告訴過你
Hey, Lee, something I never told you about me.
我討厭他媽的警察
I hate fucking cops!
好吧  咱們都當好人  來  好好說
All right, let's be nice guys, come on. Let's be nice.
我們不想死  你們#$%^&（聽不清）
We don't wanna die, we don't want anyone to die.
你就像金髮弗蘭肯斯坦
You look like a blond Frankenstein.
放下你的槍  狗娘養的
Put your gun down, you son of a bitch!
211？
211?
對  211
Yeah, 211.
該你上了  "瘋狗"
Here you go, Mad Dog.
奶奶個熊
Holy shit!
- 媽個逼的  - 他媽的咋回事？
- Motherfucker! - What the fuck is going on?
這幫人是誰？
Who are these guys?
他媽的槍放下  放下！
Put your fucking guns down! Put'em down!
放下  媽個逼的  放下！
Put'em down motherfucker! Put'em down!
我操
Fuck you!
他媽的槍放下
Put the fucking guns down.
你的真實想法如何  我對付李怎麼樣？
How do you really think I'm doing with Lee?
你開玩笑  老兄  他愛你
Are you kidding man, he loves you.
你並沒有覺得我在拍他馬屁吧  對嗎？
You don't think I'm kissing his ass or anything, do you?
不  你揀他愛聽的說  那跟拍馬屁不一樣
No, you're saying what he wants to hear. That ain't the same as kissing his ass.
對  我是說  我看過《裝在屍袋中回家》  我喜歡它  我沒騙那哥們
Yeah, I mean, I saw Coming Home in a Body Bag, I loved it, I'm not lying to the guy.
沒騙  所以不算拍馬屁
No, that's why it's not ass-kissing.
你所做的是真誠的
What you're doing is genuine.
他也知道
And he knows it.
我喜歡你  克拉倫斯
I like you, Clarence.
向來如此
Always have.
以後也會
Always will.
放下
Put them down now!
Put'em down!
把槍放下  媽個逼的
Put those guns down, motherfuckers!
戴姆斯警官
Officer Dimes.
放下槍  媽個逼的  放下槍
Put'em down, motherfucker! Put'em down!
戴姆斯警官
Officer Dimes!
什麼？
What?
戴姆斯警官
Officer Dimes!
啥？
What?
這事跟我再沒有什麼關繫了  對吧？
This has nothing to do with me anymore, right?
好吧
Okay.
所以我要走人了
So I'm just going to leave.
你們自己處理這些  好嗎？
And you guys just settle this by yourselves, all right?
閉嘴  待在原地別動  埃利耶特
Just shut up and stay the fuck put, Elliot!
你怎麼知道他的名字？
How do you know his name?
他他媽為什麼知道你的名字？
Why the fuck did he know your name?
你這坨狗屎
You're a little piece of shit!
以後20年你別想演戲了
You can forget about acting for the next 20 years!
你的職業生涯他媽的完了
Your fucking career is over!
拿出你的演員工會卡燒掉
Take your fuckin' SAG card and burn it!
你這小逼養的
You little cocksucker!
我待你如同兒子  你他媽的拿刀捅我的心窩
I treated you like a son! You fucking stabbed me in the heart!
操  操你  操你媽
Fuck you! Fuck you! Fuck you!
媽個逼的  別動他  媽個逼的
Motherfucker, don't touch him! Motherfucker!
我操
Fuck you!
科迪
Cody!
克拉倫斯
Clarence!
親
Sweetie!
寶貝
Baby!
好了  你  拿霰彈槍躲在沙發後面的  出來！
Okay, you with the shotgun, behind the couch! Come out!
操你自己屁股去[意大利語]
Screw yourself in the ass!
這傢伙是意大利佬
The guy is a wop!
我說了從沙發後面出來  你他媽的意大利佬  馬上
I said come out from behind the couch, you fucking ginny. Now!
婊子養的[意大利語]
Son of a whore!
我說了從沙發後面出來  懂嗎？聽懂沒？[意大利語]
I said to come out from behind the couch. Okay? Capisce?
等等  等等（意大利語）
Wait, wait....
動作慢
Nice and slow!
來了[意大利語]
Here I come.
靠  這人打中我了
Shit! The guy hit me.
狗娘養的射中我
Son of a bitch shot me!
親
Sweetie!
別丟下我死
Don't you die on me.
你會沒事的
You're going to be okay.
我需要救護車
I need an ambulance!
操你媽  我要把這婊子的腦漿崩上天
Fuck you! I'll blow this bitch's brains to kingdom come!
我需要救護車
I need an ambulance!
閉嘴
Shut up.
操你媽  我在流血
Fuck you, I'm bleeding!
我給你叫輛靈車
I'll call you a hearse.
這是為了科迪
This is for Cody.
操你媽
Fuck you!
親  你還活著
Honey, you're alive!
親
Honey
我看不見
I can't see.
親  你眼睛裏有血  起來
Honey, you have blood in your eye. Come on.
操  我要一輛車  帶我去機場
Fuck you! I want a car. Take me to the airport!
我要車加滿油
And I want it full of gas!
還要一百萬  小額鈔票  要快
And a million bucks! Small bills! And fast!
我要幹掉這婊子  媽個逼的
I am going to do this bitch, motherfuckers!
比弗利大使酒店
最後美國出口
墨西哥邊境 5英里
在那天的混亂氣氛中…
Amid the chaos of that day...
當時我聽見的只有槍聲隆隆
when all I could hear was the thunder of gunshots...
我聞到的只有空氣中的暴力
and all I could smell was the violence in the air...
我回想起來  大為驚訝…
I look back and am amazed...
我的思維如此清晰和真實
that my thoughts were so clear and true.
那三個字不斷地飄過我的腦海
That three words went through my mind endlessly.
自動重複  就像是壞了的唱片
Repeating themselves like a broken record.
你真酷
You're so cool.
有時克拉倫斯問我 如果他死了我會怎麼做
And sometimes Clarence asks me what would I have done if he had died.
如果那顆子彈往左偏兩英吋
If that bullet had been two inches more to the left.
對此  我總是微笑
To this, I always smile.
好像我不打算用回答來滿足他
As if I'm not going to satisfy him with a response.
但我總是會回答
But I always do.
我告訴他我多麼想去死
I tell him of how I would want to die.
但那種痛楚和死亡的願望會如晨星消逝
But that the anguish and the want of death would fade like the stars at dawn.
一切可能會跟現在很像
And that things would be much like they are now.
也許
Perhaps.
除了我可能不會把我們的兒子取名為…
Except maybe I wouldn't have named our son...
埃爾維斯
Elvis.